the Red Hot Chili Peppers performing for
the first time with their two new
members DH on drums and Blackbird
McKnight on guitar so of course Mr
McKnight is replacing Hillel who died of
a heroin overdose about two months ago
how can you guys just carry on like that
the issue of uh of music and grief over
the death of a very close friend that we
love very much two different things you
know we've got a friend who died he
wasn't just a guitar player who was one
of our best friends in the world and we
all have to deal with the grief of him
dying and it's a very difficult thing to
do but as far as our music it's like
that's the only way we're going to keep
living is by playing music and we're not
dead you know we're still alive and uh
the way to keep alive is for us to keep
playing and that's what we're gonna do
[Music]
how many years ago
[Applause]
the best man in the world well uh the
main reason is first of all I'd like to
say
[Music]
YouTube
reformed Red Hot Chili Peppers
headlining a night at the Los Angeles
Underground club alcohol salad Dave will
be back with the alternative top 10
records a little bit later right now