hello good evening and welcome to the
mtv spotlight in half an hour you'll see
a special on ziggy marley and the melody
makers
an in-depth interview with the maoris by
chris salovich
plus live footage of the band shot at
the rock reactor festival
in belgium just two weeks ago but that's
after our weekly
mtv's summer rock 1988 which
brings you live coverage of the ping
pong festival in the netherlands
in this show you'll see the christians
at the end and in a moment the red hot
chili peppers
you've probably heard that hillel slovak
the guitarist of the chili peppers died
of a heroin overdose just one month
after the concert you're about to see
hilo was
25 years old and tonight's summer rock
is dedicated to him
how do you warm up for a gig like this
it's quite difficult
than clubs he gets into some serious
scales that spits sticks taught him when
he used to play in the band fear
jack you can usually find doing a
paradiddle on a table i i just
i psyched myself into a mental state of
delirium i go for the delirium mode of
concentration
and i see it's kind of a small show for
us really we're used to playing big
shows yeah it's one of the smallest
shows on the tour and it's kind of
disappointing
yeah it's kind of disappointing but you
know the thing is we'll play anytime
anywhere if it's a small crowd hey
you know i heard you sold your stage to
michael jackson isn't that true
he opens up for us usually that's what
he does back in the state but he's doing
good he's now on his own he has his own
tour and all that
i got to let you know marcel here he's a
great guy saw him in a movie
love is a dog from hell fine films it
was a trilogy of films yeah
i thought you did a good job yeah i
recognized i was i was in
new york city at the time so that's my
friend marcel up on the screen what do
you think about that please yeah
oh
solutions
foreign
is
oh
did you guys ever meet my friend shannon
jamie where are you
hey shaney i guess you must have left
i'll show you come here for a minute
i got this good friend of mine she's
watching on the side of the stage her
name is shannon
she's got that black hat on there kind
of cute got those long red legs
hey shaney jenny come here for one
second i got some friends of mine they
want to meet you
this isn't actually shiny but you can
meet her anyways
with the show
fight
up
i am
oh
and
okay
get away
fucking
here we go
uh the truck actually does
so
girl
a girl
oh
foreign
thank you
my nose
so we've got our little love song too so
from
us to you
fucking
real quick
my
oh
is