[Music]
where you want to go who you want to be
what you want to do just come with me I
saw God and I saw the fountain you and
me go sitting in the swis mountain me on
my me and real than the bir roing no how
R the world I feel beautiful take a
white CU life is beautiful I know I know
for
sure I know know it's
[Music]
you mother I should do not suffer I know
you're B up I'm man around the world I
have SE your
lord I know I know with
you you say hello then I say
[Music]
I
sh good good
[Applause]
[Music]
evening fall free fall free fall free
fall free
[Music]
I feel feel I feel feel
[Laughter]
[Music]
feel feel feel feel Feel Love feel
love I
feel I
feel
[Music]
[Applause]
I saw your
face
El could the
ches still i s
my a blood shot your
SP delate and w
[Music]
but give me she
will rip
right R
and going get her I got her on my
mind better the feeling is so we simply
put our Your Love scam
[Music]
blow on baby I know name for give it up
and I got I came for
univers
speaking take it make
me nothing that
[Music]
love
speak
[Music]
[Applause]
I saw your
cry dying to
get with you
of this all now
the
last going
get mind nothing better than feeling so
bad we simply put our love
[Music]
Str
baby it up I
got
univers
came take it and you make
me
[Music]
[Applause]
un
get my
mind the feeling is so we left
[Music]
I let's
go
[Music]
n
PT Club on the way to Havana I used to
make a living man picking a b now I'm a
God for the
CIA for the
US baby baby made me
loo baby baby made me
[Music]
mumo to spy on a cub T show first
stop go you make little man pick the
[Music]
banana baby baby baby
loo baby baby
[Music]
M hey
yeah
I used to make a living man pick new
banana now I'm a God for the
CIA for the
USA Baby
Baby Baby Baby Baby
number
[Music]
oh
show
stop you
[Music]
make baby baby
me baby baby me
[Applause]
m
[Music]
[Applause]
yep two finger is not a I put my middle
finger your is what I in your house now
let me SP on the straight say look got
John
your head and F the blanket she's too
free and I'm the
patient and a r and
blue I scream let me
go we all good we all live in
Hollywood and I'm spoken words were
understood up to my ass at the gate
let's get it on with the alligator hater
did what you did did what you said
what's the point you what's the
spirit BL
that
I st I know I you stay
phone way out there but I don't care
this is where
I good
we you all Hood I'm
spoking understand but I don't care this
is what I want toar not got out take
we finger paint is not a sh I put my
midle finger in monly is what I wi I'm
in my house now Li Miss is an angel and
I can't do this like better but you
can't move this Pur stain upon my pill
let's
sleep black and white and blue things
that look good
you let go
purle you
stay way way but I don't care this
is KN we good cuz we all live in
Hollywood you love Hood
smoking way out there but I don't care
I we good
[Music]
we
yeah
[Music]
a
[Applause]
[Music]
Chad
[Applause]
Smith
[Music]
what is
I don't
know is a man born in Arkansas raised in
Tennessee Trav w sing a song for
[Music]
you because your because because you
walk
[Music]
the
what is
[Music]
s Mr [ __ ]
[Applause]
[Music]
cash
talking
[Music]
about
[Applause]
[Music]
he
n
[Music]
[Applause]
a
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
don't have a
partner sometimes I feel like my only
friend is the
I the city of
[Music]
Angel am
together
I the
streets she's my
comp I
through
[Music]
know
never
don't want
[Music]
to take me all the I don't want
to
little take me all the
way oh
[Music]
it's hard
to
there's there
to that I'm all
alone at least I
have
the
love lonely I am together
[Music]
take me out the way I don't want
to like
I take me
yeah yeah
yeah
[Music]
love I got my
forever
town is where I'm some blood the sh town
I could not
get oh God
[Music]
my get my life
away where are
W
[Music]
yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
he
long long long long time
ago the wind the snow I Liv the man Liv
the man I know live the freaking name
is
sex find I
stream
[Music]
de inside got of eting standing there
with my heart on bleeding there a de in
my dick some demons in my SE good God
know that would be treason me she gave
good reason look too good not to beeing
aamy b b give it cuz she's the receiver
I want and I don't hang up until I I'm
making a feel like a
a away just
[Music]
teas leave
you a man a man need
[Music]
a
nature
nature oh I got stopped by a lady cop in
my
automobile she said get out and sprad
your legs and then she tried to
come C she was out dressed in blue she
py but I'm telling you she stuck in my
butt with a big black stick I said
what's up I suck my dick like a ram
getting ready to Dam the laugh she the
when she felt my hands on her CL so very
warm I can feel her getting wet through
her uniform roing her up on the black
and white on S as last time I spoted
like no swap team can cherry
pop
[Music]
ja
I man leave
[Applause]
[Music]
you
woman that's I love 50 purple rock M
with I'm think home me make it if you
will in your arms and your legs and your
put
the to kiss with
you I do miss
you I
[Music]
love let me down let me down let me down
let me
down Lay Me Down Lay Me Down Lay Me Down
Lay Me
[Music]
Down descending
W graceful
pleasure For Your Love there is no
me com bear with SH the
spendor
[Music]
now will leave it down just sleep he the
[ __ ] will make me break I should die
before I wicked I'm long to rock out
naked B by the ordinary time to tick a
trip cutting up a little girl with the
bull whip look at it split go snap snap
good get up in my lap the test tree the
sweetest St blowing my ass right off the
map it's so nice out here tonight I
think I stay for a
[Music]
while I think I
stay at least for one more
day maybe
night
[Music]
got for
S red got for S why to do long
[Music]
r
[Applause]
red