-Well, if you weren't confused already,
you're about to see one band play in two cities
at the same time.
Here with the song "Black Summer"
from their highly anticipated and critically acclaimed
new album "Unlimited Love,"
Red Hot Chili Peppers!
[ Cheers and applause ]
♪♪
-♪ A lazy rain am I ♪
♪ The skies refuse to cry ♪
♪ Cremation takes its piece of your supply ♪
♪♪
♪ The night is dressed like noon ♪
♪ A sailor spoke too soon ♪
♪♪
♪ And China's on the dark side of the Moon ♪
♪ Platypus are a few ♪
♪ The secret life of roo ♪
♪ A personality I never knew ♪
♪♪
♪ My Greta weighs a ton ♪
♪ The archers on the run ♪
♪ And no one stands alone behind the sun ♪
♪♪
♪ It's been a long time since I made a new friend ♪
♪ Waitin' on another black summer to end ♪
♪ It's been a long time and you never know when ♪
♪♪
♪ Crack the flaming whip ♪
♪ A-sailing on a censorship ♪
♪ Riding on a headless horse to make the trip ♪
♪♪
♪ Been a long time since I made a new friend ♪
♪ Waitin' on another black summer to end ♪
♪ It's been a long time and you never know when ♪
♪♪
♪ I been waitin', I been waitin' ♪
♪ Waitin' on another black summer to end ♪
♪ Waitin on another black summer to end ♪
♪ I been waitin', I been waitin ♪
♪♪
[ Finale plays ]
[ Cheers and applause ]
[ Music ends ]
[ Cheers and applause continue ]