you guys are particularly good at uh
covers the fact that higher ground
became such a big hit did you have to go
to stevie wonder and say we're gonna do
your song uh do you have to get
permission from him to cover it on an
album plea was saying what a good idea
it would be to to
to do a heavy metal version of higher
ground you know that was your idea and
you you were like because it was in the
80s when there was so much bad heavy
metal and flea was like heavy metal can
be so rocking you know we definitely
weren't thinking like let's do a really
you know
ambitious
courageous thing you know like for us it
was just like sounds like a cool idea
let's try it you know you're just you're
just curious like
you know what would happen yeah what
would happen yeah
this is what happened
look in that baseline flea you show off
you listen to that [ __ ] bassline
and then the drum kicks in
oh that's so nice
it's very trippy
not bad did stevie ever call you guys
and say you know i like what you did or
you never heard from him i i actually
saw him not too long ago
with a good friend of mine and and and
he came over and he said hey stevie what
did you think of that of chili peppers
did you like the way they covered higher
ground because i like the publishing
checks
i had a funny experience with him once
in a
lobby in in detroit what was that
experience what happened
well it was more like like someone
called me and said
a road manager or something and stevie
wonder's in the lobby of the hotel
and i was so excited because it's my
hero i i love stevie wonder one of my
greatest heroes and i i ran down to the
lobby to try to say hi to him thinking
maybe he'd talk to me because of the
cover and stuff and
he was sitting there and i walked up to
him and i was like stevie hi i i'm flee
i play in the red hot chili peppers and
you know i just wanted to say hello we
played in your in your played your cover
and you know and and i i love you and
and i kind of waited and i felt awkward
and a minute went by and i said it again
well i just wanted to say hi i'm fleeing
you know anyways uh
you know you you your music means so
much to me and anyways have a beautiful
day i i don't you know i didn't know
what to do i was just kidding and i
thought me you know and i kind of like
another minute went by i got more and
more and awkward and he said nothing
ignored me and i got ready to walk away
and i was kind of walked away and he
goes are you one of the members
and i was like yeah yeah i'm the bass
player and i kind of thought he was like
kind of gauging to see if i was full of
[ __ ] or not you
know oh
okay uh hi would you guys play my
fundraiser next month for the moment or
something i can't remember
and i was like you know however we could
be of service you know stevie
if we can and
and i can't remember then we chatted for
a minute or something but since then
i've met him a number of times and he's
always been really generous of spirit
and kind and engaging