wow
here
[Applause]
oh
me
solutions
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
is
[Music]
[Applause]
did you guys ever meet my friend shady
shady where are you
hey shaney
i guess you must have weft
oh [ __ ]
come here for a minute
i got this good friend of mine she's
watching on the side of the stage her
name is shannon
she's got that black hat on there kind
of cute got those long red legs hey
shaney
jenny come here for one second i got
some friends of mine they want to meet
you
[Applause]
[Music]
with the show
[Applause]
[Music]
up
oh
[Applause]
get away
is
[Music]
uh the song actually starts with trouble
[Applause]
[Music]
so
wow
[Music]
girl
oh
[Music]
so
where's that
[Applause]
oh
me
[Music]
call me
where's
[Applause]
[Music]
me
so
[Music]
[Applause]
hello
[Music]
my nose
[Applause]
[Music]
so we've got our little love song too so
from us to you
so
[Music]
me
today
real quick
[Music]
oh
foreign
shut down
[Applause]