whole music scene revolves around one
day getting to the bingo show here in
bruxle's all the bands in los angeles
the only reason they ever begin is so
one day they can come to bruxelles and
get on the bingo show have you done
anything about those dirty underwear
you've been wearing because it's really
been disgusting i've been meaning to
talk to you about it for some time those
brown smelly underwear just won't do
yeah you look like my mother even who
invented this flashy image artichoke
fart is it hard to compete with the
other uh rap acts in america like the
dev jam acts and so not really because
we're so much better than everybody else
there's really no competition
um you know most bands they try to you
know reach our level but they really
never get anywhere near it and uh you
know we're just five worlds above
everybody and there's really no
competition last year we sold more
records in the world than anybody else
we topped brew string scenes michael
jackson's records and uh we've been
drawing crowds of like 40 000 a night
every night we had to play the uh the
main soccer stadium around here whatever
what is it what's the name of it again
hazel stadium yeah hiding stadium we
played that i think 12 nights
in the middle of winter too
it was an amazing thing is that guy on
their arm jimi hendrix what um it's jimi
hendrix because i think he's a really
lousy musician and wasn't a really bad
person so i decided to put him on my arm
forever he's actually he's actually one
of our favorite drummers of all time is
fight like a brave uh your contribution
to the peace movement um well we are
very peaceful guys and any contribution
we can make toward peace we're happy to
make it because we love peace okay
that's great
hot chili peppers
[Music]
oh
don't hear us
[Music]
don't want to stop
no i can't tell you
[Music]
don't be asleep
[Applause]
[Music]
but you're gonna get away
don't tell me that i got to take a
number
[Music]
[Applause]
three
me
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
and today the