good evening everyone and welcome is raising 2015
the
my name's back speakers this year's racing executive director
strange thing is UCLA's oldest greatest musical tradition
certain 1945 as a competition between
attorneys quickly outgrew Royce hall and moved to the Hollywood Bowl
and is now held our very own billion world-renowned song writers George and
Ira Gershwin produced over 70 musicals and four films
there are more than one dozen Broadway shows including the landmark
opera Porgy and Bess in 1936 the Christian Brothers adapt to their title
tune from the musical
strike up the band as UCLA's new fight song renaming
strike up the band for UCLA in recognition of the contribution to UCLA
the George and Ira Gershwin awards the spring sing in 1988 to recognize
lifetime musical achievement in the industry here tonight since you suckers
award recipient please allow me to invite up to stage the George and Ira
Gershwin award director marina's story
good evening born in Grand Rapids Michigan
spending most of his young life Los Angeles this
artists went from a short span child acting career
to becoming one of the most influential musicians in the alternative rock
them the early at the age of twenty
iniki disco pounded the Red Hot Chili the
which aunt as lead singer and lyricist over 30 years
their 1983 debut
the Red Hot Chili Peppers released a total
10 studio albums including blood sugar sex magic
Stadium Arcadium their most recent album I'm with you
and fan favorite single such as denny California
under the bridge give it away other side
countless others Anthony's near
writing style has evolved with his own personal journey and his
cover the spectrum relatable social and cultural
such as friendship romance loss
angst and the journey overcoming struggle as the band's music has blended
many styles between punk fun rock and alternative
Indians led the band
what is considered one of the most legendary Pathan evolution
music 5 hours have been certified multi-platinum in the United States
and the Chili Peppers remain one of the best-selling man
all-time with over eighty million records sold worldwide
him towards including six Grammy Awards
10 Video Music Awards and the 2000 for lifetime achievement
the Red Hot Chili Peppers were inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in
recognition under Mike cops
in addition to writing recording and touring Red Hot Chili Peppers
Anthony number other accomplished including the 2004 publication New York
Times bestselling autobiography
scar tissue and recognition music cares for his dedication to helping others
with addiction and recovery
tonight we celebrate over three decades
his contributions to the music industry so let's take a look back at his red-hot
career
we've been here for the Red Chili Peppers
leavin about my home guard tissue please welcome
many kids
day
E
missed
she
did
beautiful and powerful an amazingly indescribable
sonic way
the
I'm happy you see I am station and the Student Alumni Association
it is my great present with the same way please welcome to the stage the 2015
recipient
George and Ira Gershwin Award for lifetime musical achievement anthony
keith
the
this is so weird this is just strange
Anna you just never know with the day is going to bring
on before I get carried away here
sidetracked into a surreal day dream
I would like to say that this is really
on behalf from the Red Hot Chili Peppers
you can I have been lucky enough to write a bunch of songs but always with
the band
and that's my band in those are my brothers in
we started something together and Medina maybe cuz I
I'm I went to school here every year in nineteen eighty
the
the single me out the man who really this enough whatever this is
accomplishment through this work in progress or whatever you wanna call it
it's from a band I am one of whom is
with me tonight
said I you know i think thats
receiving a lifetime achievement awards
quite dangerous and potentially
detrimental to your career because
I don't want to be done at all and I don't want to be
the
and i wanna be
irrelevant or disconnected for a from the things then
inspired me to begin with his in North
it happens to and poets and popular song writers you know the start of them have
such a great connection live and what it is to be
connected to humanity in the common experience and then we
we get successful in reaction you know the words that are coming in suddenly
have
really nothing thank live in fear that a little bit no
trying to figure out how to stave that off for as long as possible
but I am grateful nonetheless and I'm grateful for the experience
what it is to be
in those pointed out for someone who writes songs because that's what I love
to do in
I don't know in Georgian I really think about this tonight
but I get the back relate to one of the 2i would relate to ira
because he was the lyricist in
you know when I was a kid I really did love
words I loved the look upward sound
word the meaning of words that were Jinnah words
the inherent rhythm in million word seem to come within
the innuendoes like my dad was in the words he taught me about where the
word and when I was
12 I think I I proclaimed in I'm
I'm going to be a singer when I grow up and the
the weird part about that is I was a horrible singer
and I really had no musical Aki min
word town or anything at all but I like the way that music made me feel and
that's why I said that I didn't think
who is this great singer when I would listen to the radio
and I was your music fill me up so strong
me feel so alive and so turned on and excited
love ideas that even at a very young age
I knew okayed let me just be involved in this somehow and then it turned out I
had no Middletown
but quietly along the way
I love my very best friends world which
ending on the instruments and learning about music in practicing every day
and
and i was just around them long enough so that one day they like keeping your
words
to use over their income make a song with
in that that kinda how it panned out for me and then I got to learn a little bit
about music along the way really I just got lucky
I got lucky by being in the right place at the right time with my friends
and watching their work ethic in their dedication
and this whenever I had to offer seem to blend with that
that was my experience and I
very grateful and very appreciated that anybody cares and I
and I hope did last for a long time right now
right now we're in the middle writing a bunch of new music to make another
record
the wanna
Miami you know my George is called sleepy
and
he shattered his elbow so we've
we've sorted in in on the hiatus and that's why we're doing things like this
thing things happen for a reason and and now I'm just gonna shut up and we're
gonna play a couple the songs and just thank you