- [Lyrics] A lazy rain am I,
The skies refuse to cry
Cremation takes its piece of your supply
The night was dressed like noon,
A sailor spoke too soon
And China's on the dark side of the moon
Hit it now
Platypus are few,
the secret life of Roo
A personality I never knew,
Get it on
My Greta weighs a ton,
The archers on the run
And no one stands alone
Behind the sun
It's been a long time since I made a new friend
Waiting on another black summer to end
It's been a long time, and you never know when
Waiting on another
black summer to end
Crack the flaming whip,
a-sailing on a censorship
Riding on a headless horse to make the trip
It's been a long time since I made a new friend
Waiting on another black summer to end
It's been a long time, and you never know when
I've been waiting
Waiting on another black summer to end
Can't stop, addicted to the shindig
Chop Top, he says I'm going to win big
Choose not a life of imitation
Distant cousin to the reservation
Defunct, the pistol that you pay for
This punk, the feeling that you stay for
In time I want to be your best friend
East side love is living on the West End
Knocked out, but, boy, you better come to
Don't die, you know, the truth as some do
Go write your message on the pavement
Burn so bright, I wonder what the wave meant
White heat is screaming in the jungle
Complete the motion if you stumble
Go ask the dust for any answers
Come back strong with 50 belly dancers
The world I love, the tears I drop
To be part of the wave, can't stop
Ever wonder if it's all for you
The world I love, the trains I hop
To be part of the wave, can't stop
Come and tell me when it's time to
Sweetheart is bleeding in the snow cone
So smart, she's leading me to ozone
Music, the great communicator
Use two sticks to make it in the nature
I'll get you into penetration
The gender of a generation
The birth of every other nation
Worth your weight, the gold of meditation
This chapter's gonna be a close one
Smoke rings, I know you're gonna blow one
All on a spaceship, persevering
Use my hands for everything but steering
Can't stop the demons when they need you
Mop tops are happy when they feed you
J. Butterfly is in the treetop
Birds that blow the meaning into bebop
The world I love, the tears I drop
To be part of the wave, can't stop
Ever wonder if it's all for you
The world I love, the trains I hop
To be part of the wave, can't stop
Come and tell me when it's time to
Wait a minute, I'm passing out, win or lose
Just like you
Far more shocking than anything I ever knew
How about you
Ten more reasons why I need somebody new
Just like you
Far more shocking than anything I ever knew
Right on cue
Can't stop, addicted to the shindig
Chop Top, he says I'm going to win big
Choose not a life of imitation
Distant cousin to the reservation
Defunct, the pistol that you pay for
This punk, the feeling that you stay for
In time I want to be your best friend
East side love is living on the West End
Knocked out, but, boy, you better come to
Don't die, you know, the truth as some do
Go write your message on the pavement
Burn so bright, I wonder what the wave meant
Kick start the golden generator
Sweet talk but don't intimidate her
Can't stop the gods from engineering
Feel no need for any interfering
Your image in the dictionary
This life is more than ordinary
Can I get two, maybe even three of these
Coming from the space to teach you of the Pleiades
Can't stop the spirits when they need you
This life is more than just a read-through
[applause]