no the killer video cameras the little
itsy-bitsy video camera did is that just
a little
[Applause]
[Music]
I'm pretty good I used to like the
school like us movie star from
I know and stop the camera like say
speaks English came back there to say hi
so sorry man pain
[Applause]
[Music]
how are you excited about the gig and
[ __ ] dude it's not even raining bad you
guys don't even know what a monsoon is
even though idea this is it's not even
raining it's dry right now how do you
get the money
yeah I'm so stuck because I was caught I
called the promoter last time friends
with the cat and I'm up dude what's up
you get a cancel and they said this
morning they'll make the announcement
but check out the little don't you do is
that just a little bad boy camera
yeah you can do anything you want with
it yeah that's it's a total digital
[ __ ] camera
210 you get one here too bad two bands
checked out
yeah check it out
[Music]
no no I mean it's right now tonight
tomorrow you can't to play yeah you
gotta play with it
[Music]
you can hook up to TV your computer does
[ __ ]
[Applause]
it's a [ __ ] video camera [ __ ] you're
not here yeah it has a little table I'm
Adam I'm
Adam how you doing buddy how are you I
didn't even wake you who's this little
bad boy
oh my god
[Music]
alright
be care you know they don't have normal
toilets
sure check it out Oh God yeah I'm just
like recording a little get
[Applause]
[Music]
in fact Perkins friend you mustn't hi
we're just like doing the whole gig it's
part of the environment [ __ ] it it's
pointing out there's a core I got this
sound working it killer you know like
zero playback I uh I
I bought it I I'm a street painter I do
this spray paint art you know guy in
Venice does the spray paint planets in
Perriman yeah that is me well he's my
teacher so I came out here and I've
worked 12 hours a day for the last 10
days to buy this camera to record this
concert
no
you put it out in the computer see can
you hear the sound let me see that last
time took the last one yeah okay it's
zooming okay now you can go up and down
how do you put it on July
15 seconds of delay or
[Applause]
I got one song about so when the Jews
and what else does it do it's the
cameras new report how much
comfortable when they get on cameras
[Applause]
just joking I care I care
and that's a photo and that's that's a
photo and you can download that on the
Internet to your butt and listen to the
sound it makes I
just got this I woke up at 9:00 got to
store it tan got to the chart that's the
picture of the camera is that a traffic
I love it I'm so happy with my little
toy and more times Paris Italy Germany
Switzerland and Amsterdam
and now I can record it all I'm going
again I'm gonna do the whole game
- cool
so what did you guys think what do you
guys came to town the day before
yesterday or something that's right
where have you been staying in tokyo
[Music]
fuji right out here this is the city of
fujiyoshi
have even like going and talking to the
vehicle the locals so mellow
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah no no no no I know I just you know
I just had to come see hello I'm gonna
take a little picture very much just a
favor yeah all right - cool I'm so
bummed about the harm so I love my
little boy
[Applause]
[Music]
if you send the guy some rage against
machine
I haven't ever seen - they look like
everything yeah okay
call and go say hi real quick time
adding right
[Music]
over this
yeah I didn't see the show I just got
here so cool thanks man
[Music]
[Applause]
that killer
chicken cool I love this thing
[Applause]
thanks guys
[Music]
[Applause]
the boss