hmm
[Music]
[Applause]
do
uh
[Music]
so
[Applause]
[Music]
the reservations
is
[Music]
for any answers
is
[Music]
[Applause]
so smart she's leading me to ozone
[Music]
to go to meditation
[Applause]
is
[Music]
oh
just like you
[Music]
anything i ever knew
[Applause]
[Music]
maybe even three of these coming from a
space to teach you about
can't stop the spirits when i need you
this life is more than just a
read-through
hmm
[Music]
just
is
[Music]
i love my baby today
just really
[Music]
yes
[Applause]
[Music]
never made it up to minnesota north
dakota
[Music]
when i left
release
[Music]
she's
yes
[Applause]
[Music]
hmm
so
[Laughter]
[Music]
so
all around the world
state of pennsylvania
[Music]
for sure
wake
up me
[Music]
hey
just come with me
[Music]
my life is beautiful
[Applause]
is
[Music]
so
[Applause]
all
[Music]
run
shaking
my story charlie's making me charlie's
making this
everybody do the twist
get the message off these fists move
around like a scientist
lay down get this
[Music]
pick it up
so much
[Music]
charlie's making me
is
[Music]
all i ever wanted to do
[Applause]
[Music]
charlie's making this
is
[Music]
yes
[Applause]
[Music]
mmm
now
[Music]
sometimes i feel like i don't have a
partner
sometimes i feel like my only friend
is the city i live in the city of angels
lonely as i
am together with cry
[Music]
i drive on the streets cause she's
now that is
[Music]
like i did
take me
[Music]
it's hard to believe that there's nobody
out there
hard to believe
that i'm all alone
at least i have her love the city she
loves me
lonely as i
am together
[Music]
take me
love
me
[Music]
is
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
got
once you
[Music]
the thing we need is never all that
often
[Music]
are you alone
the stones
[Music]
is
giving up
[Music]
wanna go oh time
you