this beautiful old mansion on Laurel Canyon Boulevard in Los Angeles has some
interesting vibrations
legend has it that it's supposedly wanted supposedly the Beatles drop ass
in here for the very first time
Jimi Hendrix played here a while and there is as legend has it
a panel click mishaps to another house by Graham's
there was once our own by Harry Houdini said in the vibrations were interesting
enough for the LA band the Red Hot Chili Peppers they stayed here for two months
to record the album blood sugar sex magic
whose idea was it to report on the health and camp out in the hills
arm I believe it was initially the cubans idea there is one that we are
joined in any way
every year was such a cool thing to do just big old haunted house up in the
Hollywood Hills
and i was just such a peaceful consonant place to be
it was a know we're all living there
and recording there and it was just such a relaxed natural way to record music
just wake up in the morning and meter black Christian Gourcuff you let the
paper on plane was just like a natural extension
living as opposed to going into this release sterile environment in having to
deal with you know secretaries know you can get going and no she wasn't there
before you in a messing up the ride
he gonna like Paula Abdul could've been a using a technician before replacement
trying to record music and Paula Abdul's vibe was still in there
get up with corporate spineless general are
it's absurd and some had a it was just a wild place
China's kids 2 p.m. anything to chat not have
News wrote up a new bike when sessions are injected a net
effortlessly on my team
better one has Stephanie I'm I have to admit there are a couple nights rest up
really late and had a net yeah cherished yes seriously
do I think it when he got his nickname back to check out the corners and find
out what's gone forever
working professional or scary room right where the facts and there was a go-slow
who made about me
and it was just a little bit spooking and you know after they complete their
scares when I step and I'm
but never have I dotted okay affect my daughter and she wasn't an occasional
much happening engine 3m non-cancerous mornin don't mean is that
Steve Kean and one host
you here in the courtroom no no I don't think that would be right
I woohoo
who well you
who all you
cow any ok well pumpkin anyway
okay anybody no for 20 min
one is called My Own Private Idaho and it was directed by Gus Van Sant
made many drugstore cowboy and
term has a story about shot the album cover term
he and he shot pictures from around cover I'm
and we use those with some graphics which would in my head chef michael is a
tattoo artist
so it's an interesting combination harness their
more like are you from director typing
to the same big balking mean
tattoo artist his mentor to from bank
keeping key does love I work actually did I'm
commuter station and I and a record cover confirmed please governor and we
went over here
hmm 113 had his there yes want him
their core countries from yes when I got this affair Pacific Northwest packing
from the northwest and natural after her and thereby Vancouver BC to hire an ETA
hey there
Travis you know that this is a bill story about an amazing psychedelic this
time and you run their
and at regular intervals are often so they got specifically with my daughter
reminder done by Joe Jordan Hollywood California
relevant Clara who is my wonderful beautiful body just got back from a trip
to Canada
Claire and appear is Jimi Hendrix
and you as a friend of mine Jimi Hendrix
genius was a friend yes I am spiritual connection Omega
telepathic and spiritual alright I'm can be flexible with winding snake
this animal snake at least are things done by the chinese guy unabomb bob
roberts chinese guy and how liberal rag
smile him chip market investment in the under
get there for public place me and Michael Warren Amsterdam
the Confederation or I have a few official arusha
is a Canadian girl that I fell in love with and married
and I we since divorced and you know I love camden I married a Canadian
butter and ended up in pure misery so I don't think about it I get a tattoo on
my head
you can see a lot about sure my head and shoulder going on come up with the idea
of when are left on what is it
it to from Skullcandy and I have a pair back with the Belarusian broad
ever they require
really like that we gotta amenable to call them on it has been unleashed and
its gonna hurt you that
to think that the trip is a good the millionaires by the time that
they will get through this am we're doing right back to get a shot the ball
they'll your is my pool I know you're a millionaire already but
million and happiness after mister for minimum 10
going on
addicted to pick cotton back to be right where
no I we made a really good record people lot to people right that's great if not
really proud that we made a good record
the record is like straight from the heart real shit
no I mean it's not it's the motion record that we made
and really proud we covered a lot of emotional territory in Misrata varieties
channels mood units are real
and song