[Music]
californication
you know not that it matters but it was
in the things uh day i wouldn't say dave
quit the band it just stopped being a
productive and fun
and creative experience for everybody
it was just kind of it ended naturally
like uh you know this is
this is not really what it's supposed to
be so let's
let's try uh moving on
but you were supposed to be very
productive for one hot minute
we were you was we were supposed to be
he was
oh he was yeah well he's you know he's a
good he's a he's a great guy and a great
guitar player and
that just kind of ran its course and
didn't really feel uh
didn't feel like what we were looking
for and then you know suddenly out of
the blue
fleece suggested that maybe we could
play with john again which was a
a terribly exciting prospect which
it was the furthest thing from my mind i
didn't think that was really a
a potential reality and then it turned
out to be so
it was a lucky day and john what was
your first reaction
what was the first to ask you to come
back fling
i came over to my house and we listened
to some music
um i was playing with some records and
then he
said uh something i wanted to talk to
you about uh
how do you feel about being red hot
chili peppers again you know i said
i said yeah yeah that sounds like it
could be good
and uh and we just started talking about
it
and we just seemed excited about it you
know
a lot a lot of uh
a lot of things have changed since since
the time that i quit
and we've we've joined together now in a
in a
way of uh we have a unity and a
closeness that
that uh that we had we'd gotten really
far away from before
can you define can you explain what is
different now into the papers
yeah yeah me and anthony were friends
now
we weren't friends back then one
difference it's one difference
and it's a big difference it's very
important
yeah it's very important for a band to
be friends with each other and to talk
to each other and
to enjoy each other's company because
you've got to be around these guys all
the time you know
so if if somebody's
you know somebody's way of life or
way of thinking isn't gelling with yours
it's a
it's a struggle and a pain to to go
on tour and to make music you know just
doesn't happen whereas when you love
each other you write songs you're proud
of each other you
you know you enjoy each other's
performance on stage
we weren't even looking at each other on
stage before i saw a videotape of us
back then recently from what show troy
new york
and we just we paid no attention to each
other nobody in the band paid any
attention to each other because it got
to the point where flea was so mad at me
and anthony for not but especially me
for
not trying at least from to me it seemed
like just me maybe you got to vibe from
him too
he was mad that that we weren't trying
to make it work
our relationship that we were just that
we weren't
trying for the sake of the band to be
friends we just were
like content to go around like hating
each other
and so he i fleece started being so mad
at me for that
that my fleet's relationship wasn't was
going downhill too
now we're all equally we're all happy to
be around each other and
be around you know and that makes for
making
good music you know at the time that he
asked me to join the idea of
getting together every day and making
music with people who i love who have
who share a similar vision of what the
purpose of music
is was just sounding like the greatest
don't you think that sometimes it's
safer to be in a band just on a
professional level
and not personal level i'm not worried
about that and i wasn't worried about it
when i quit
and it's never been like that for this
band
it didn't start like that and it never
really got to that point and
i don't think anybody was ever looking
for a uh
a safety net to be in this band i mean
i don't think it would be very good if
if that's the arrangement you know if we
just got together for
for making music it just wouldn't be the
way it is
yeah i don't need that kind of safety
you know
it's not the way i approach everything
but one of the reason uh for your
debater
was the pressure
no the pressure on the band yeah no i
didn't quit the band because of the
pressure on the band i
i think at the time since i quit
and then me and flee or me and anthony
we never really
discussed the reasons why they were just
asking me why and i just said i have to
you know it's just a feeling now i
understand why i did it
like and uh
but like so they used they probably said
that like uh
pressures of uh being successful john
couldn't handle it
flea i've heard him say thanks to that
effect you know
but it's not but that's not the case it
had nothing to do with the pressures
you know there's no nobody was putting
any pressures on me
because i wasn't i decide like i wasn't
doing any interviews at that time
only pressures were going on tour and
playing music and i loved playing music
every night
but the going on tour part of it is no
fun if
the people you're on tour with aren't
your friends you know
it starts to just be a drag you know
so so yeah i mean it's not i don't
really consider them pressures
you know i just i didn't like doing the
whole thing that you do being in a band
without you know and until
you take this is this bad departure
as a betrayal was it was it painful
it was definitely painful and i didn't
understand what was happening
you know i wasn't really sensitive
enough to the situation
to know what he was feeling or why he
was doing the things he was doing
you know my vision was a bit narrow at
the time and
and uh i just wanted to keep playing i
really liked the record that we made
um i was probably missing something that
we had from the past when we used to go
play live shows together and
have a great communication on stage and
i wanted that again you know very
desperately
you know because it was just something i
was missing and
uh you know i definitely resented him
for a while when he quit but it was it
wasn't coming from a
a focused place of understanding it was
just kind of a free-floating resentment
like
you know this just sucks and you know
why does he have to go do that and
but much more powerful to me at the time
was just a real
sense of loss and and i knew that
somewhere in there that i had done
something
that was you know that was selfish
enough to where it didn't work
and um you know i just missed him and i
was pissed off at him and
you know i cared about him and and
really you know that was a lot of stuff
that happened and i guess you're curious
about it because
it was a big explosion at the time but
you know never
in my wildest dreams did i think that
that we'd come together again to play
music
no i never i never considered it you
know i
my main thing was just that i wanted
john to know that i that i did love him
and that
i didn't want either of us to die
without you know reestablishing a
connection
and um and that was my biggest fear is
that you know either i'd get a call one
day saying
john is dead and i would have never been
able to tell him that even though she
got [ __ ]
up i still love you and i still care
about you and i think about you
so you know just the first day that we
started playing together i felt
a huge blessing and and then it just got
more and more fun
and you needed
in mind to reform a winning team a
winning team yeah we had it in mind to
reform a winning team
but you know that's that's a sort of a
an intellectual prospect that is easier
said than done you know we definitely
wanted to carry on and
and we tried many times you know we
played with so many different people
after he left
and and never found uh
a beautiful chemistry you know we we
never found a chemistry where we were
happy and where we were creative
and where we all understood each other
and and had a desire
every day to play with each other you
know it became more of
just something to do because we were
supposed to do it
and uh and that changed you know the
minute we got together like this again
it just became
we're doing it because we love it yeah
we had to we tried to get a winning team
uh
you know there's there's not a lot of
first uh first-round draft choices out
there
for instance was it obvious to you to to
use again
rick robin as a producer was it obvious
uh
for one hot minute or for this record
it was not obvious it was not obvious we
we became so in love
with the the experience of playing music
and writing
songs over the summer we were very
committed to it
and suddenly we realized that we were
onto something
very special and that the songs we were
writing were as good as any songs we had
ever written
and we wanted a producer who had the
same kind of
all-or-nothing enthusiasm for for the
record we're about to make
because that's all we cared about and
that's all we were focused on and at
first we maybe had doubts
we were devoting our whole lives to the
record and rick was
seemed like he he likes doing a bunch of
things at once you know
he normally produces a couple albums at
one time plus runs his record company
and we felt that he might be too
distracted you know
that he couldn't give himself to us 100
right
so it crossed our mind but in the end
it was a the greatest thing to to work
with him
because he fell in love with the music
just like we did and probably worked
harder and longer
and and more from the heart than than
any of the other times we ever worked
with him
you know he's do right now as we're
sitting here he's in new york
you know doing uh extra work to make
sure that everything is perfect for the
mastering of our record
which is not like rick to do something
like that
[Music]
blood sugar sex and magic was a massive
but do you consider the album as a
masterpiece
or is it just a step in your musical
evolution
yeah i mean i i just think of it as the
songs that we wrote
during a really great year you know
during like uh
probably the happiest time of my life
that i've ever had
uh you know through the songs that we
wrote during that time period and
we recorded them you know and then the
period ended
like i don't see the f no i don't see
the final things being a masterpiece but
i see it as you know another great album
there are probably a couple of songs on
that record that could have stayed home
and not made it on the record
but what about the song like under the
bridge um
was it in a way a curse or a blessing to
write a song
i think that song is probably close to
being a masterpiece considering it's
only like two and a half minutes and
it's really like
is that yeah it's real short i had no
idea i had no idea
yeah and it's really powerful you know
i'm just like
i'm very happy we wrote that song i mean
that song is a very sad song you know
when anthony first came in with the idea
for the vocals and the lyrics were just
like oh
jesus yeah it was it was funny because
i i wasn't going to take it in i
definitely wasn't going to take it in
to the to the band practice and then uh
and rick
looked at it in my notes and he's like
well hello what about this and i was
like ah
please please let's move on and he said
no i think you should go in there and
sing that
and the day i went to sing it it was
just chad and john flee was late or
didn't come that day or something and i
was just so prepared for them to kind of
go okay
thanks for sharing but you know we got
other things to move on to and they
they got sad but it was not a curse
it wasn't a curse just because you have
a popular song that
you know people associate your band with
it doesn't matter in the end
but in a way you were ashamed to to
express those feelings of loneliness and
sadness
uh i was not it wasn't shame yeah
you're not in shame just shy because you
know he
like is you know
because why why was i shy because i'm a
shy guy
yeah i mean it's just you know you you
uh
you express things a certain way with
your words and
and uh up to that point you know
you've been like used to more expressing
like good celebrating kind of feelings
celebration of life kind of feelings
and and uh writing lyrics that were just
totally you know about lonely about how
lonely he was and sad and feeling
without a friend
was just a real deep kind of part of
himself to bust out with you know
but he did it and we made it into a
really good song
you did a lot of covers on stage or on
record
what were your reaction when all things
cover under the bridge
a reaction yeah were you proud or
uncomfortable maybe i would have
regretted writing it if i heard it i
don't know i've never heard it
what the all saints version no no right
what about you
um i was more amused than anything else
you know i didn't i didn't i didn't you
know
swell up with pride or it didn't make me
angry i just
i just thought it was uh amusing
[Music]
do
sometimes i feel like i don't have a
partner
sometimes i feel like my only friend
is the city i live in
the city of angel
lonely as i am together with
i drive on the streets cause
she's
[Music]
she knows who i am
is
[Music]
take me
it's hard to believe that there's nobody
out there at least
[Music]
take me
yay
[Music]
i could not get it
[Applause]
[Music]
robust
so
[Music]
um i read in rolling stone magazine that
you work
at bixler all together to
just to practice and making music and
for one
augmented i guess if i can remember you
were in hawaii all together
the ban i mean uh you need from time to
time together
all the band and just play music for the
pleasure of it
uh yeah those were two different
experiences though
you know when we went to hawaii it's
because we were we were looking to
establish some you know communication
and experience together
that was just different you know when
when the when we went to big sur it was
just
flea and john and myself and it was
purely for fun and we had
one small mission which was to write an
acoustic song
that's one just one single song with
acoustic instruments
and to go surfing and to you know have
some good food and listen to music on
the way up and flea just got in a new
truck
so we were breaking it in that was
purely a road trip
you know just for the sake of fun and
you know it was
yeah we were there for a few days and we
just
only you know a few hours like three or
four hours were probably spent writing
that song you know
the bulk of it just being uh anthony
writing lyrics will mean flavor taking
naps
usually in the into the credits um
the old band sign the songs but how do
you work actually
the whole band sang the same songs oh
sign the sound
yeah how do you work actually is it
always a a song
came always from a gem between the all
of us
of you well it's always never
anything everything it's always
different sometimes i start a song
by but with an idea on the guitar and
plea writes a bass line and chad writes
a drum part and then we all just talk
about what other kind of section the
song needs and
then then that comes along and then
anthony starts seeing something that
makes us think of something else and
you know or our song could come from
chad just playing a drum beat and
us playing along with him and you know
they come all different ways
all different combinations yeah there's
no set way there's no formula
and there's no boundaries it can go
wherever it wants to go
and in the end the way we figure is that
we all
eventually put into it so like we
thought that california
i mean we thought that uh the song road
trip and needed drums chad's
input and the reason he gets the writing
credit on that song is because he
said no drums she said it doesn't need
any drums and we figure that's worth the
credit for that
that's a good point that's a good point
of view genius
um i wish she'd have that idea more
often just kidding
um can you can you summarize the album
uh
the mood of the global rule of the brand
new album with
few words can we summarize the record in
a few words
yeah is it about love the feeling of
loss or
lost yeah l-u-s-t oh no loss
alpha double s
oh loss uh that's that's a lou reed
record
magic and loss you familiar with that
one yeah
i'm not really big on summarizing it was
we had so much fun making it
it felt so good to be back together and
to be
going in the direction that it would
have only happened with
getting together every day like that you
know we couldn't imagine what we were
going to come up with and
it just felt so good to come up with
these songs and
um i think it's as good of a record as
we ever made
it's based on everything not just loss
it's it's
more based on the opposite of loss you
know
uh you know re-blossoming of sorts right
yeah because you talk over and over
about the pleasure you
you had making the album but
the album seems to me very sensitive and
in a way
a bit uh serious and
and and
hurtful in a way yeah well there's
pleasure to be had with those things
yeah i mean a lot of the time the music
that some of the music that gives me the
most
that makes me feel the happiest is music
that's uh
that people say is sad or depressing or
something
but that's because you know me
with music you can you can uh recreate
all kinds of feelings that
that exist in the universe you know
and and uh
and i think on our new album has a wide
spectrum of them you know
it's not any one kinds of songs i just
i like the the way that we've gone
that we've gone about ex uh
letting the feelings come through us and
expressing them with our instruments in
a way that sounds really uh
modern but at the same time takes roots
from the
kind of uh the kind of originality and
colorful playing that people did during
the periods of
new wave and punk rock and but at the
same time
it sounds modern and without having any
electronics
and still each section has its own
texture and feeling to it
i'm real proud of all that the song
californication
i read those lines destruction leads to
a very rough road
but it also breathes reads creation does
it
apply to you to the papers i mean
to the papers yeah yeah it applies to us
for sure
for sure i think it applies to
everything in the universe but
specifically that
to me was uh descriptive of of
my personal life and of my life in this
band and
just
all of those things that that didn't end
up destroying us
[Music]
you know led to this so and this was
very creative
very creative time in all of our lives
but do you think it's very necessary
do i think it's very necessary don't you
want to change it
change my change the way the way you you
need
difficulties well i didn't try to create
it in the first place it just happened
yeah i mean there's certain things in
faith you have no control over you know
faith like is the way it is you can only
force yourself upon your fate in
simple ways like what you eat and and
how much you smoke
and and what you say to your friends and
what you say to the people you pass by
in the street
but all the rest of it it's just stuff
that happens to you you know
the songs you write you it's not your
decision you know
that whether or not you go through hard
times whether or not
somebody dies whose friends who's a
friend of you is
whether or not you you start destroying
yourself like
these are things you don't have all
saying you know
but you need four years to make a brand
new album
is this novel
and we don't we didn't need four years
i mean once we got together it was a
year ago today or something like that
that we got together so
and and when we talk to you in a year
from now we'll have a new record
yeah this record didn't take us four
years to make
took us about nine months
and in the recording of it itself took
only about three weeks
that's very quick you know yeah um
in the future we're going to try to put
out a record every day
so i can wait for that
um i wrote an interview of flea where
where he said that
he is very uncomfortable with rich
people
because when he grew up he ate rich
people what about you
are you more comfortable than he is
that's a funny thing to say
makes no difference to me makes no
difference to me
i would say i'm less comfortable around
rich people than i am around poor people
but
i don't know i mean you know i'm the
same way as play i didn't have money
when i was a little kid we were in
welfare and stuff
that means that's like where you get
money from the
government because you can't get a job
when you're a kid and stuff
um
have you ever fallen in love with a rich
girl
no nope have you ever fallen in love
with the rich girl
neither okay
what about you um no i fell in love with
a girl who is dirt poor
in a week-to-week style but you know i'm
friends with flea and
flea's pretty rich so i guess i'm
comfortable with that
[Music]
so
the kids
[Music]
here
don't know
[Music]
step is
is
[Music]
me
yes
[Music]
[Applause]
um
[Music]
[Applause]
now
[Music]
hmm
[Applause]
[Music]
for your
what i got father got it put it in you
feel it don't stop
[Music]
continue
right now
[Music]
give it away
so
[Music]
is
give it give it away give it away
[Music]
you
[Applause]
[Music]
gotta give it away
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
close your eyes and i'll kiss
all over myself
[Music]
it
make it to the moon
[Music]
close your eyes
is
[Music]
[Applause]
i
[Music]
mr
who you talking to
[Music]
anybody wanna call me
you'll never know
[Music]
can't be understood
[ __ ] will not be told to go
[Music]
so
um
[Music]
so
[Applause]
[Music]
wow
[Applause]
[Music]
um
welcome back
[Music]
all around the world
hallelujah
but i know
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
i know
[Music]
oh
cause life is beautiful
[Music]
is
[Applause]
[Music]
ah
welcome back chad
[Applause]
where do you go home tonight
go home tonight be very nice to your
mother
because your mother loves you very much
uh what makes you think they live with
their mothers
well for all those of you who do live
with your mother
[Music]
[Applause]
there must be something in a way i feel
that she
don't want me to feel
but still she doesn't call me
i don't care
[Music]
is
a mountain never seemed to have the need
to speak
[Music]
the sweetest
true
[Music]
hmm
it would not stay
[Music]
is
oh
[Music]
now
[Applause]
[Music]
um
and that was something completely
different
[Music]
uh maybe the song is gonna be dedicated
to joe d'alessandro tonight
[Music]
so
and if you want these kind of dreams
[Music]
it's the edge of the world in all
it's understood
[Music]
is
information
[Music]
not far away
two
[Music]
[Applause]
me
[Music]
so
me
[Music]
operations
is
[Music]
[Applause]
so
[Music]
good
so
[Music]
is
three
[Music]
thank you
is
[Music]
[Applause]
mm-hmm
[Music]
so
where i please
[Music]
is
the angels in my dreams
[Music]
is
oh
[Music]
mmm
so
[Music]
indeed
and take away myself
[Music]
just yeah know
where i am
[Music]
[Applause]
so
[Music]
oh
yes
[Music]
me
oh
[Music]
shake it to the river
oh
[Music]
thank you very much
[Applause]
[Music]
mm-hmm
so
[Music]
is
can you hear me
[Music]
is
me
[Music]
is
[Applause]
bigoted
[Music]
yo very good nice to meet you
wax postman tartary basement jacks suede
the offspring
silver chair luscious jackson gaydad and
the heliroches
and i know it didn't come too easy