this video is brought to you by slip
disc records with great bands like lucky
whiteness Dude Ranch Playboys his new
album no music no Betty's no lucky
classic Outlaw country western recorded
from 1946 through 1968. he influenced
everyone toured with Les Paul and Mary
Ford what else oh yeah he even inspired
Elvis Presley
and for all you punk rockers out there
no apparent reason recorded in 1985 what
Society denied with two new upcoming
releases slated for four twenty twenty
twenty two snap Bubba Waltz and lucky
threes shut up Richard available on all
platforms Apple music iTunes Spotify
Pandora and Amazon
fingers
we're trying to start a fan with him
okay that's cool
last night
yeah
oh no I didn't work guys
why don't you do that foreign
dude
I'm a little nervous
um
foreign
oh
yeah
you're gonna rock them
no I don't think I want to do that
tonight
come on Gary says there's bonus in there
if you guys get off 15 minutes early
the next is Indy
I did
mark this strap for some reason hey what
do you want to do get rid of your back
it's like scratching drop it look like
Jimmy Page okay
right
I got him there on top of your base
oh [ __ ] and Tommy on top of police
a little pair of shorts with some socks
will you go grab them would you grab my
bag too is my bag right there yeah
there's a um orange there's an orange uh
backpack behind the drum Rider on the
floor
two minutes
let's get that happening slow down
look at that meat and potatoes
slow chunk
of chocolate
can we hit the punk rock dude let's
explore Madness although the tempo was
perfect last night
thank you
very much
I'm John Stan
get another copy of this too get the
[ __ ] out of here
that's why we're here
I can play with tape that I made when I
was in eighth grade
here we go everybody ready
Hey Kevin can you lock up this back room
or at least
I'll get someone to sit back yeah
slowly slowly slowly you guys ready
let's go
hammer down
give me the kisses
everybody
knows wait
wait a minute
Gary that's it
okay
boys
foreign
all right
thank you
foreign
oh [ __ ]
thank you
hi everybody
it's really great
just come on with God that's the coming
down
um
you guys
ought to know one thing
somebody may seem like he's lost his son
and that's because he's dating Pee-wee
Herman Corey actually dates Me Stevie
Herman right now
good
way
this is
not gonna lose
baby you're in the place
foreign
do do what I wanna do
I do
okay
thank you
and he created an option
you know that or you look good [ __ ]
whenever you can lick [ __ ] while you
were doing auctions
this song is dedicated to the Lakers
even though they lost tonight they're
still going to win the World
Championship again
foreign
you love me
thank you
today
foreign
no time
we're moving out
assistant
by Charlie Chaplin
my best
because
myself
never back in the back
foreign
there's nothing
wrong
good job
let's go
short come on
give me one more
thank you
you're in the bus
yeah right
behind you back
together
this is
tired
thank you foreign
goodness
around the list
get away
for telling you mistakes
foreign
now
what
oh the classic
okay
videos
foreign
baby
you go you guys
otherwise
you don't want to be no Super Friends
about a while
together
girl okay
that was funky I hate to say that was
very funny
dildo master of all pilgrims
birthday
s
since that's open today
foreign
let's do it
on your birthday baby
baby
girl
I was trying to explain to a reporter
today that we're not sexist we just sexy
thank you but you got a big dick so you
make up with your information
it's really nice and it's a big nice
and my scrotum you know how some girls
can pick up quarters with their vagina
he can actually pick up quarters with
his penis head
all right
foreign
breathe over there
we demand step two and your family again
you know
foreign
ready to know
give me give me give me
I need the boys
do it again
thank you
foreign
get out of here
everybody back
there now
foreign
thank you
what's so funny
he's on the road again
okay
all right
thank you
foreign
all right
machine
thank you
I'm about to do it again
outstanding
and then you know I didn't even think
I can hear you coming out of the truck
ain't no [ __ ] cameras in here man
I'm rocking Rock'em socks
guys yeah
um
Orange County
if we do URL I would say that's the only
thing we should do let's go do something
sweaty yeah
yeah
thank you very much
thank you
foreign
okay well uh yeah right yeah okay
haha
excuse me
foreign
thank you
with me
foreign
thank you
very much
all right
um
across down
we'll see you there
bye bye we love you TV Land