you thank you Tom
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
welcome to the global citizen Festival
2023 live from New York City's Central
Park today a stellar lineup come
together as Global Citizens to demand an
end to extreme poverty now for the plan
planet for equity for food and for jobs
thousands of voices Amplified by artists
Advocates and world leaders will unite
to demand change we must take action now
with performances from Anita
Conan Gray
Sophia Carson riracha of stray kids D
nights Jungkook
Ms Lauren Hill and Red Hot Chili Peppers
please welcome Global citizen
ambassadors Rachel Brosnahan and common
and actor director writer and activist
Natasha Leone
[Applause]
[Music]
Global Citizens how are you guys doing
[Applause]
I think I heard that how are you guys
doing
you are the brave ones we are back here
again on the one day of the year that we
get to come together rain or shine to
tackle the challenges that affect us all
year after year I keep coming back to
this stage and the reason is pretty
simple it's because I am a global
Citizen and so are all of you
today
whether you're in the crowd
or on the stage or watching at home know
that this is no ordinary moment and we
are all in this together with a purpose
we're excited about the incredible
lineup of performers who are here today
but we're also excited for the change
this moment can bring to the world
that's why we're really here you see
actions speak louder than words ever
could and today we're gonna see that
action in real time my very close
personal friend Jordan Fisher where are
you
all right enjoy right there with you in
the audience holding down the floor
that's right and we are inviting all of
you here
that's right and all of you at home to
join us as active participants in the
fight for a better world Listen even in
the pouring rain am I right guys
Jordan stay strong in the rain backstage
is already buzzing in today I'm going to
be chatting to all the change makers
policy makers and do you guess it your
favorite artist as they fight for Equity
to end extreme poverty and of course for
glamor Justice
okay so Global Citizens tell me are you
ready to take action
one more time are you ready to take
action
[Applause]
I am Juan Gary I'm Katie I'm Brianna I
am Sabrina and I am a global citizen
speaking to you today not as an actor
but as a global citizen just like you
I've been thinking a lot about what that
really means to be a global citizen
being a global citizen for me is about
empowering the voices around me giving
those who feel voiceless an opportunity
to express themselves and advocate for
the issues most important to them I'm a
global citizen because I believe in the
power of people and Collective Strength
because the forests in Canada and
Ecuador Brazil and America deserve to be
protected because girls in Afghanistan
Iran deserve access to an education
because kids and Rwanda Somalia and the
Pacific deserve to not be faced with
hunger every day
Global citizen is proof that no matter
who you are or where you're from you can
take meaningful action on the world's
biggest challenges together we can end
extreme poverty in our lifetime together
here today we can all take action we are
all Global Citizens
[Applause]
where are we going oh
we're back
how y'all feeling
Global Citizens how you feeling
and you say New York City
all right well back for round two so
look the challenges we're facing when it
comes to equity climate change and the
hunger crisis are not new but they have
been made worse in the last three years
and we will need Collective Global
action to address them today
735 million people are going hungry
735 million people
are going hungry and despite the cause
for help internationally the global food
crisis has not been addressed by our
world leaders we want world leaders to
face up to hungers so we are going to
put our faces up to them everyone here
can join the petition calling on world
leaders to overhaul the current food
system so that farmers stop losing their
crops children no longer have to cope
with malnutrition and millions of people
can access the food they need
almost 60 000 Global Citizens have
signed a petition already but we want
more
scan the QR code you see on the screens
now and upload your face
yo let's show our leaders that we United
in responding to this Global food crisis
it'll come it'll come up the QR code
will come make sure y'all participate
make sure y'all all a part of this get
involved
listen
I'm gonna add my face to the petition as
well all right as long as well as a few
others behind me we're gonna go ahead
and do this right here you ready one two
three all right y'all see the QR code up
there right do the same thing
do the same thing pull out your phones
take some selfies let's all get on that
petition together
[Music]
now Minister Chris France has been an
incredible Champion for Education over
the years but we know that the numbers
are still very Bleak especially with
girls who are still out of school around
the world what is France doing to
address this
for France at president macron education
is a top priority that's why I am here
during this sdg Summit we promote the
sdg4 that is the sdg of education so
here today I'm very proud to announce
that France will continue to support
with 40 million euros that will be
dedicated to the U.N agency
education cannot wait so we are planted
we call all of the parties to do the
same what an incredible commitment from
France thank you so much and of course
CU Global Citizens continue taking
action as you can see it breeds results
right here right now we can help fulfill
the promise of a digital world an
amazing connected landscape for everyone
for over a decade
we've committed to empowering students
and teachers with the latest technology
and training
Verizon helping fulfill the promise of a
digital world
please welcome award-winning actor
playwright and Global Citizen and un
women Goodwill Ambassador deny Guerrera
Verizon chairman and chief executive
officer Hans Vesper and Verizon
Innovative learning school students
Angie and naoki
hey everybody
[Applause]
and I just like all of you am a global
citizen
in my life I've made it my mission to
advocate for the underrepresented voices
of the world
and I'm standing here with Verizon to
speak up for all the children
who deserve a chance to excel in school
millions of kids around the world are
missing out on an opportunity to connect
to learn and become whoever they want to
be because they don't have access to
Internet and Technology
a year ago on this stage we shared our
mission for our variety of in Verizon
Innovative learning initiative to
promote digital equity and inclusion in
education today alongside my friend new
friends Angie and Aoki we are who are
the students in our program we're here
to share proof with all of you that when
the right tools are accessible the path
to success becomes clear
[Music]
[Applause]
learning curriculum is building circuits
that can create wind or light from
electricity and hope to One Day become a
biologist
my favorite part about the Verizon
Innovative learning Lab at a school is
robotics I'm working with buttocks
almost every day and I'm an active
member of the robotics Club at my school
whoa
we're thrilled to announce the door
digital inclusion initiative have
reached three and a half million
students and we're not stopping through
this work we will reach 10 million youth
with digital skills training by 2030.
these kids right here on this stage are
our future they're what we're fighting
for so let's give them all they can get
to succeed for the Next Generation
[Applause]
please welcome Global citizen Ambassador
Rachel Brosnahan and the Executive
Director of Education cannot wait
Yasmeen Sharif
[Music]
[Applause]
again
I have shared the global citizen stage
with Yasmine many many times over the
years because I believe in education
cannot wait I've also seen the
organization in action restoring
Children's Health hopes and dreams
through access to school
thank you thank you Rachel we love you
so much education cannot wait we deliver
education to shielded emergencies and
protracted crisis and we are able to do
that thanks to you Global citizen you
are making a difference your actions
made it possible for us to Rally
commitments of February from Men of our
great Partners like Germany Denmark
Norway Italy the U.S Canada and the UK
and so many more and this week as we
just heard France Paris France pledged
40 million euros
and Finland pledge another 8 million
euros to help us the power missions yes
but we still need to keep going there
are 22 million kids out there we need
more funding and education is our best
hope as the Next Generation you have to
help us resolve the wicked problems
facing Humanity we can make it it might
drain you keep shining
please join us in calling on governments
and the private sector to commit new
funding now thank you thank you thank
you thank you Sean
[Applause]
please welcome to the stage Global
citizen Ambassador science educator and
CEO of the planetary Society Bill Nye
and climate Justice Advocate Shia
bastida
yeah it's a beautiful day yes it is
beautiful day we love that song
just delighted to see so many of you out
here
uh she and I are gonna play a little
game
uh I'll throw out a random word and I
want you to give the audience an
alternative that are better for our
planet
here we go
plastic bottles that's easy reusable
bottles uh long showers
um time showers one song Max
but let me do one bill fossil fuels
fossil fuels well there are several
alternatives to fossil fuels I mean you
have solar energy wind energy hydropower
geothermal energy biomass energy I mean
I could go on and on
[Applause]
so many Alternatives why are water
leaders still deliberately passing laws
that subsidize and expand fossil fuels
good question fossil fuels pose a grave
threat to our planet burning them
releases carbon dioxide and other
greenhouse gases into the atmosphere
which act like a heat trapping blanket
which drives global warming it is a
recipe for a disaster for both our
environment and our health
precisely in Paris on the global citizen
power our planet stage I joined my
fellow Advocates calling on world
leaders to commit to climate financing
and to sign up fossil fuel treaty
against the destruction of nature but
we're still waiting for Action we must
urge world leaders to sign on to a new
fossil fuel non-proliferation treaty
which would ensure a just an equitable
transition away from fossil fuels
I've been advocating for this for a long
time the scientific fact
the scientific fact is that fossil fuels
account for a staggering 86 percent of
carbon emissions
but there's also a moral side to this
conversation we have to protect our
planet for all of us
just last week
one week ago we had the largest climate
March in four years with over 75 000
people and we had one sole demand
and fossil fuels thank you all very much
stay warm out there
[Music]
[Applause]
we love that song Carry On and fossil
fuel
our beautiful planet
since this time last year there's been
more evidence than we ever needed that
our planet needs Urgent Care
we must act today to save our tomorrow
we're calling on private sector
companies to cut emissions in line with
science-based targets that means
reaching Net Zero by 2050.
invest in low-income and climate
affected countries because people on the
Forefront of climate change are the ones
that have contributed the least to it
and have the most to gain from
investment in its Solutions we need
projects that really deliver viable
options for clean energy like solar
panels and wind farms and help for
smallholder Farmers to adapt and survive
for the first time in 25 years extreme
wealth and extreme poverty have sharply
increased simultaneously people live in
an extreme poverty cannot afford to
invest in climate action for a crisis
they did not create
so we are calling for ambitious
solutions to Urgent and devastating
problems we have one planet we share one
Earth and we each have one lifetime to
make a difference these companies have
already signed our pledge will you join
us
Global Citizens please welcome the
executive secretary of the United
Nations framework convention on climate
change Simon Steele and Community
Storyteller from Wildlife Works Jane Oco
[Applause]
New York City is this wet enough for you
is it wet enough for you
at the United Nations we're trying to
keep the climate negotiations process
honest and get all the cabinet rooms
boardrooms living rooms and festivals
all over the world to deliver on climate
action we at the UNF Triple C can only
do that with your support so I'm
counting on each and every one of you to
do your bits and to get those around you
to do you to do their bits too
we have to work together to address this
crisis
this year Global citizen has partnered
with Evelyn to make a positive
investment into nature and cover the
estimated carbon emissions of the
festival
Evelyn represents high impact Forest
conservation projects like Wildlife
Works and I'm joined Now by one of their
Community storytellers Jane o'coff
how you feeling
Mambo Global Citizens my name is Jen
okot and I have seen how effective
Community centered Forest conservation
projects can be at stopping
deforestation and delivering on the
sustainable development goals at the
local level
redplus project in the Democratic
Republic of the Congo for example
partners with over 50 000 people living
in the forest
they are protecting their forests and
safeguiding biodiversity by creating
sustainable economic opportunities for
community members which benefits every
citizen in the world
[Music]
[Applause]
indigenous and community-led projects
like this address the drivers of
deforestation so join me in listening to
indigenous people and local communities
living in threatened forests
[Applause]
with their leadership we can create
Equitable solutions for climate change
that will change our future for the
better thank you
[Applause]
please welcome secretary for the
indigenous peoples of para Pui Tempe the
minister of indigenous peoples of Brazil
Sonia guachajara and the governor of
para Elder babayo
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
I am here today representing the Amazon
rainforest backed by the power of my
ancestors in the voice of an activist
our home and our people are under threat
and I'm here to issue a call to action
s
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
we will only succeed in Saving the
planet if we share the responsibility
just as it's not fair that a small group
of leaders decide the fate of us all
it's also not fair that the people who
have contributed the least to climate
change are impacted the most by it
Menches
[Applause]
[Music]
is
[Applause]
[Music]
our indigenous knowledge must be heard
and we must demand climate Justice
receive the strength of the forest its
rivers and its lands received this
message to reforest our minds new
beginnings and resilience call on the
spirit of the Amazon she will answer
[Applause]
oh this is
Brazil
um
foreign
[Music]
I have heard your calls for action and
I'm here to respond to them the state of
para in Brazil has made protecting the
environment a priority since being on
stage in 2021 we have created two new
protected regions bringing the state's
total protected area to 21 million
hectares our goal is to expand protected
areas by one million hectares by 2025
with a primary focus on safeguarding
indigenous lands and eliminating illegal
deforestation we will also restore
another 5 million hectares of forests by
2030 and we call on other world leaders
to commit to protecting our mother earth
too
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
please welcome Global citizen Ambassador
nomzamo mbata and the founder of her
Village Inc Chantal Alison kante
when I say Global you say citizens
global Global
[Music]
[Applause]
not every single day 800 million people
have their periods
who here gets their period
[Applause]
that was weird yeah but it's okay you
see how weird that is period poverty is
stigmatized every single day
and yet there are people that can't
afford the products they need to manage
them safely
in South Africa where I am from it's one
out of three people
period poverty is the lack of menstrual
education and access to period products
no access to products can mean missing
school and more more many people around
the world experience this right here in
the United States nearly one in five
girls have missed school due to a lack
of access to period products
but of course our sisters are coming
together to change that
foreign
right now we can get creative in ending
period poverty
as a dancing influencer it brings me
great joy to promote education to tackle
stigma and to step up as a Force for
good for my fellow black sisters not
only here in South Africa but around the
world for decades PNG has proudly
championed gender equality and with the
always keeping girls in school program
we are committed to breaking down
barriers for a future in which every
girl can reach her full potential
[Music]
four years ago PNG four years ago png's
always brand made a commitment to help
end period poverty since then with
partners and people like you they have
donated more than 270 million period
products in 28 countries
that kind of impact is huge but there's
more work to be done when I was a
teacher in Harlem I saw some of my
students struggling to afford period
products which is why I founded her
Village we help parents learn how to
have real and honest conversations about
menstruation and we've supported
thousands of girls with period supplies
here in the United States I am supported
in my fight thanks to Partners like
always and its period Heroes across all
50 states join us in taking action to
Imperia poverty once and for all In Our
Lifetime and now
Let's Get Loud for one of South Africa's
original always blood sisters who's
bringing the movement to New York along
with local sisters Amina farida and
nikayla from the Grassroots Community
Foundation
[Applause]
[Music]
sisters
sisters always do what's right sisters
never leave behind sisters always keep
in mind these sisters who need help to
go to go to school to spike and flow
because sisters lead to and they know
this Blood can't stand between us no and
together with a pad a day your blood
sisters will lead the way for 10 years
now and still counting we never stopped
helping because always donates one pad
every time you buy one pack
join the blood sisters and walk your
sisters to school one pad at a time
always
[Music]
[Applause]
please welcome Katie Holmes and actor
activist and entrepreneur Sophia Bush
hi
hello Global Citizens
can you all Brave the rain in Central
Park today is truly inspiring
we are all in this together and today
I'm thrilled to be here with my friend
Sophia
to call for action on women's
empowerment around the world
for countless women and girls around the
world empowerment starts with economic
independence as an advisor and an
investor in women-led businesses I know
firsthand that women-owned businesses
are growing two times faster than the
national average and women of color are
driving that exponential growth
but right now women only receive 16 of
conventional business loans which is
just over four percent of the total
funding allocated Financial equality
enables women to break free from poverty
setting off transformative Ripple
effects that posit positively impact
every corner of society this empowerment
translates to increased educational
opportunities for children
better health care for families and
thriving communities if women and men
around the world participated on equal
footing the global economy could grow by
an astonishing two and a half trillion
dollars so investing in women-led
businesses will not only increase
economic independence but it's also a
good business decision
so let's keep raising our voices because
gender equality isn't a women's issue
it's a human issue
thank you thanks
Talent is evenly distributed in our
society however opportunity is not today
not 20 years ago today more than 100
million girls worldwide are denied the
basic right of access to education and
girls are more likely to live in extreme
poverty it's time we all do more to
develop a more sustainable economic
model that lets girls tap into a safe
and prosperous future at worldwide
technology we are passionate about
developing the next generation of girls
who will inspire and lead the world
working with young girls to equip them
with the cyber security skills needed to
keep us safe in a digital world
partnering with Empower to break the
cycle of poverty and provide girls with
tech training and job placement teaming
with Girls Inc to help low income
communities explore exciting I.T careers
and scaling that work globally funding
and expansion of a girls hostel in India
to equalize the girl to boy ratio in the
aramira school as Global Citizens we are
doing our part to spark generational
advancements for girls through action
and accountability doing our part to
make a new world happen
you would have missed it but we were
shimming in this tent Come Rain or shy
now Senator Coons you've been an
incredible active participant in
securing U.S funding for humanitarian
and developmental programs I'm
interested to hear what kind of steps
can Americans take to hold their elected
officials accountable to the kind of
changes that they want to see thank you
for the question Global Citizens we need
you we need you to text to call to write
to visit your elected officials if you
want to see change if you want to see
support for development for humanitarian
Aid you need to get up and go to the
district office or the DC office of your
elected official and hold them
accountable for delivering what the
world needs and deserves what's more to
say
no one sees the world quite like an
airline but the world we see below us is
changing fast that's why Delta is
committed to Net Zero carbon emissions
by 2050. it's why we're getting rid of
4.9 million pounds of single-use
plastics annually and it's why we're
accelerating our Push To Source
sustainable aviation fuel because we
know a thing or two about getting where
we need to be and it's time we all got
going together
please welcome the director of the
sustainable Skies Lab at Delta Airlines
Sangeetha Sharma
hello Global Citizens it is wet we are
here and I am so happy to be here with
you today taking action together to
create a more sustainable world
that's right
at Delta we are flying toward our 2015
Net Zero goals and part of the way we're
doing that is by driving continuous
innovation through our sustainable Skies
lab
within the lab we're pushing Innovation
at Delta across every facet of the
operation and through transformative
Partnerships
we're looking to make changes every day
that can help us fly more sustainably
from the products you use when you fly
Delta to the design of the future
aircraft themselves
that's why we're proud to work with
Partners like Joby one of the driving
forces behind electric aircraft
Airbus a leader in research and testing
fuel-efficient technology and someone
somewhere to create sustainable
artisan-made amenity kits on board
to date we have eliminated about 4.9
million pounds of single-use plastics on
our planes
that's right
25 of our ground service equipment is
fully electrified and we have saved more
than 10 million gallons of fuel thanks
to our carbon Council
[Applause]
but we want to do so much more
we at Delta will continue to work with
innovators across travel and Aviation
including you to make our goals of Net
Zero a reality
[Applause]
please welcome the minister of
International Development Norway
we must all tackle the global food
crisis together
so I'm thrilled to announce that Norway
is pledging 90 million dollars to the
international fund for agricultural
developments
[Applause]
you know Africa has abundant human and
natural resources
but its countries continue to import
food for billions of dollars every year
because its farmers are lacking access
to the resources that they need
now Norway's pledge will help
small-scale farmers in Africa get the
tools and technologies that they need to
adapt to climate change
join us in calling on other member
states to increase funding for the
international fund for Agricultural
Development right now
[Applause]
in the pouring rain suddenly the tent
smells delicious and it is just shining
I am here with Anita ladies and
gentlemen oh my
my contain myself and he said you're
helping us today to kick off the
incredible show at Global citizen
Festival what made you want to perform
on the stage today well I think my
country Brazil I mean we have the
Brazilian Representatives here already
and um I'm here for my country I'm here
for the Amazon I'm here for my fans here
in this rain there's not gonna stop our
party and I'm excited speaking of the
Amazon now it is known as the lungs of
our planet what more can we do to
protect it well I think try to protect
the people there the indigenous people
the communities there are born and their
their only reality is the Amazon and now
when we get there and we invade the
Amazon it's kind of like we're getting
into their business and we should
respect that we should protect them and
make sure we keep them safe you are a
worthy Global Superstar and Ambassador
ladies and gentlemen
[Applause]
[Music]
please welcome Global citizen Ambassador
Rachel Brosnahan and 2023 Global citizen
Prize winner wangari kuria
hello again we are standing here in this
torrential downpour it's a very dramatic
Global citizen Festival this year
thank you all so much for being here you
have no idea how much this means that
you've all braved this rain to be here
today so thank you we are here at a
pivotal moment in history where we have
the power to come together and make sure
that no single person ever goes hungry
again
I am a small holder farmer in kajiado
Kenya and the effects of climate change
on our farm have been devastating
actually I wish I could borrow some of
this rain to take with me back home but
Africa only emits two percent of the
world's carbon yet we suffered the
impacts of climate crisis the most
how can we fight poverty and
malnutrition when we are caught up in an
inescapable Loop of the crime crisis
government the U.N and the private
sector must come together
to invest and adapt in mapping out a
comprehensive food system that will
serve for the next 100 years
Norway has just committed to doing its
part to make sure small holder Farmers
like wangari get the funding that they
need to mitigate and adapt to the
effects of climate change and now it is
time to join the face up to hunger
petition if you haven't already the QR
codes are on these two screens on the
side of the stage so can everyone take
out their phones really quickly please
join wangari and I right over here on
the edge
[Applause]
what
it's being blocked
I'm gonna take care of that bank a
selfie with me really quickly right now
everyone join wangari and I I'll get the
I'll get that unblocked for you ready
ready one two three
and let's turn around we'll get everyone
in it ready yes
okay
we're gonna beat that Ellen selfie one
two three
smile
thank you all scan the QR code when we
get it unblocked on the screens and show
our leaders that we are united in
responding to the global food crisis
thank you
the audience today is filled with people
from all over the world who took action
to be here including Pratt Serena and
Brianna from Accenture who are
passionate about getting involved to
make a difference guys thank you so much
for being here how does your work with
Accenture make you a global citizen
Jordan my work enables video to be a
global citizen every single day you see
I'm a part of a team that brings the
best of Accenture to partner with ngos
and businesses to empower underserved
communities all over the world beautiful
oh
well there are a lot of big issues in
the world today and it's important we
leave behind a better generation for uh
tomorrow and
um you know it's important to be a
global citizen because we're here to
create change
um and know how we can make action today
great
and change is exactly what Accenture is
all about in fact that's what we do we
help our clients our communities and our
people become the next best versions of
themselves I know I speak for everyone
when I say thank you for your work thank
you for taking action it takes drops
like here out today like this rain to
make a difference and we are doing that
here everyone give it up for Accenture
guys now please welcome to the stage
accenture's U.S Northeast Market unit
lead Stuart Henderson alongside some of
the Accenture people making an impact in
their communities
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you Jordan we are so happy to be
here today representing more than 700
000 people of Accenture worldwide we
encourage all of our people to embrace
projects they're personally passionate
about and can impact with their skills
in the Philippines our teams are
building homes for people with
disabilities in India we're working with
women-owned businesses to make them both
profitable and sustainable and in
Denmark we're exploring how AI enabled
voice activated assistance can help make
life easier for visually impaired
today I'm pleased to announce that
Accenture is committing
4.5 million dollars over 40 months
in support of Aspen's institute's Global
opportunity youth Network this program
provides young people in Brazil Colombia
India Mexico and South Africa increased
access to productive and dignified
employment and skills that help them
Thrive at work
extensions people are taking action
because they believe they can make
positive change happen
I know that all of you here believe too
so let's keep taking action together
[Applause]
right here right now we can drive
positive change
from Skilling for technology careers to
designing solutions for some of the
world's greatest environmental and
social issues we can create lasting
impact in communities around the world
and at Accenture our people over 700
000 of us are passionate about getting
involved to help build a more inclusive
and sustainable world because when we
all come together we can make a
difference at scale
please welcome to the stage director
general of the international labor
organization Gilbert F huangbo and the
founder and CEO of phenomtech sciency
learning kosana butalinkosi marsukum
[Applause]
around the world
inequalities are widening
today we have 4 billion people
I have no social protection
and more than one in five
in the 15 to 20 years old are not in
education
not in employment or training
this is not inevitable
it can't be changed
we can achieve greater social justice
especially if we include young people in
the action
half of the global population is under
30 years old and Africa is the youngest
population in the world we need to
commit to empowering Africa's youth
through quality education but it's not
just about providing them with
classrooms and textbooks it's about
equipping them with the knowledge and
skills they need to innovate and lead
from there we can work together towards
creating inclusive employment
opportunities
[Music]
Global solidarity is going to be key
the United Nations
together with the international labor
organization created the global
accelerator on job and social protection
for just transition in a way to mobilize
the creation of 400 million decent jobs
and provide social protection for the
billions of people that lacks it
I'm so delighted to let you know that
this week
at the U.N General Assembly
three new Donald countries agreed to
support the accelerator and we expect
more to join us very soon
so keep raising your voice in calling
for initiatives just like this together
we can demand decent work green jobs and
access to Quality education
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
when enough of us act together we're an
Unstoppable Force for good we are
changing laws
ousting the corrupt building platforms
to speak out on galvanizing through
action together we are changing the
world the human right to speak out some
protest together is fundamental in the
fight for democracy and Justice and yet
some companies file strategic lawsuits
against public participation
[Applause]
[Laughter]
an unscrupulous and devious strategy
some companies use to silence us and
misdirect our energy to the defense
against bogus lawsuits so that we no
longer have the resources to fighting
justice but Global Citizens we are
fighting for our rights and supporting
others to fight for this
we are fighting the whole idea of slaps
to liberate Global Citizens everywhere
and we are so thrilled and proud that
tonight these companies are pledging to
fight slaps by refusing to even engage
with them
we will fight on
[Music]
Nature has always taken care of us I
know its power and its beauty and how
much it does to care for and protects us
all it's time for us all to do the same
[Music]
please welcome Anita
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
forever
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
my love
[Music]
[Applause]
yourself
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
with this bag though
[Music]
[Applause]
hello New York City
[Music]
foreign
keep talking
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
thank you
guys
we're here tonight for a very important
reason
the Amazon is so important for the
planet
it provides life to so many specials so
many specials and
it's critical in taking carbon out of
the atmosphere which is key to fighting
climate change
I must we must support and invest in
indigenous Community working to protect
the Amazon
so that we all have a healthier planet
to live on
[Applause]
I'm singing this for the Brazilians
[Music]
[Applause]
who knows this one sing with me
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
Channel
this is
[Music]
hospitals
please
I wanna hear the Brazilians in the house
[Applause]
[Music]
together
foreign
[Music]
thank you
nothing much
[Applause]
[Music]
sit down
[Applause]
[Music]
everything
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
anyway
Crazy Prices
[Music]
[Applause]
you're standing
[Music]
show me
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
YouTube
surprise
[Music]
ah
a
thank you so much
[Applause]
[Music]
I know I know it drives you crazy
oh baby baby
[Music]
foreign
when the girls
[Music]
who's this
thank you
[Applause]
okay I don't know how I'm still standing
right now I just want to Bow
[Laughter]
Conan gray welcome to your first Global
citizen Festival how are you feeling I
feel amazing thank you for having me in
the pouring rain right
we're already wet the show Will Go On It
must absolutely now part of taking
action is standing up for what's right
what role do you think the youth have in
playing a positive impact for change
everything I mean we're the next
generation of people and we have to
fight for the climate because this is
the only planet that we have uh to
guarantee a nice life for for us but
also for future Generations absolutely
Justice everyone
fires you that you're looking forward to
kind of meet today oh God everyone
everybody here today are such special
people and also everyone in the crowd
coming out in the pouring rain for a
positive change I think it's an amazing
thing so everyone
and that's everyone and we're about to
have a fantastic show yep
please welcome actor producer United
Nations messenger of peace and founder
of the Charlies therein Africa Outreach
project Charlize Theron and 2023 Global
citizen Prize winner Deja boss
[Music]
[Applause]
you all look really good wet
well
I'm Charlize
[Music]
and I'm a global citizen
[Applause]
wow I'm loving the colors out here today
thank you for coming out in the rain
y'all I know it's been hard but we love
seeing your beautiful faces out there
yeah for sure are you guys ready
[Applause]
who are you here to see give us a big
yell
[Applause]
I understood some of that yeah I heard
some of you
[Applause]
wow you guys are amazing amazing amazing
thank you all so much all right well a
little something here I grew up in South
Africa where yes where not only is there
an issue of Access to Health Services
to many but there's often stigma and
discrimination connected to these
Services especially for young people and
especially when it comes to sexual and
reproductive Health Care
improving the reach and quality of the
services is part of our mission at the
Charlize Theron Africa Outreach project
but this isn't just a South African
issue
it's a global one around the world an
estimated 4.3 billion people of
reproductive age will not be able to
access as at least one essential or
reproductive Health Service in their
lifetime
and oftentimes as young people we don't
even have the information we need when I
was just 15 I realized that my school's
sex ed curriculum in Tucson Arizona
hadn't been updated in decades I'm
talking since the 80s and it wasn't
medically accurate didn't even mention
consent so when I worked with committed
citizens just like you all to rewrite it
and since then I've been fighting for
Reproductive Justice feminism and
working to redefine Sisterhood in the
digital age with Gen Z girl gang
yeah
yeah from South Africa to the United
States we are still fighting the war our
grandmothers and our mother's wage to be
treated as equal human beings
we are still facing the same assault in
our Reproductive Rights and threats to
our essential health Commodities like
birth control
but we cannot lose our courage now we
need it more than ever if we work
together we can enact change demand sex
education and birth control for all
young people
[Applause]
decriminalize and destigmatize access to
abortion
amen including self-managed care and be
an ally and work with us to demand our
leaders invest in sexual and
reproductive Health Services for all of
us
and now you all have been very loud so I
need you to help me send a message to
the people in power all right our bodies
Our lives our right to decide our bodies
Our lives our rights to decide our
bodies Our lives our right to decide our
bodies Our Lives
bye guys
[Applause]
please welcome actor and activist Eddie
Izzard White House environmental justice
advisor Jerome Foster II and climate
Advocate Shia bastida
[Applause]
[Music]
the vast majority of people around the
world now realize that climate change is
very real and it has devastating impacts
this year alone we have seen floods
fires and hurricanes unlike ever before
people look to the United States as a
powerful country and ask if they are
doing enough well as someone from Europe
I'm here to say that these people with
me on stage and everyone here in Central
Park and everyone watching from home
around the world you are all doing
unbelievable work
[Music]
U.S leadership is essential in the fight
against Global hunger inequality and the
climate crisis which is why we all join
together in asking Congress to not cut
foreign aid budget in 2024. after we
rose up and pasted posters all across
New York City we targeted our
Representatives
we reminded our leaders that they cannot
turn their backs on today's Global
challenges that women and girls around
the world are the first to face the
impacts of the climate crisis hunger and
poverty and we need to stand up together
because issues are all interconnected
[Music]
[Applause]
and that the U.S must uplift Global
Frontline communities affected first and
worse by the climate crisis and are
continuing to be affected today we must
seize this moment to become a Beacon of
Hope for the future because we called
out Congress and we came together and
they're taking action but Congress has
now responded but much more action is
needed
foreign
[Music]
there are many of us in the United
States Senate who will continue to do
everything we can to ensure our country
continues to support critical
initiatives that Advance our shared
mission of global peace and prosperity
your voice is needed to ensure leaders
remain committed to fighting for foreign
assistance
keep taking action and calling for U.S
leadership and know that I'm in Congress
doing the same
just last month I visited a refugee camp
in Kenya where a quarter million
refugees are struggling with hunger and
elsewhere in Kenya I visited a factory
making plumpy nuts called rutf for
children who are suffering from severe
acute malnutrition our Aid makes a
difference
[Music]
we have a responsibility to help those
in need and I will always fight to
protect those who cannot protect
themselves
in this year's government funding bills
we have an opportunity to make
investments that will save lives and pay
for dividends for years to come stay
strong and let's keep up the good fight
to end extreme poverty Global Citizens
we've heard your calls for action on
Hunger inequality and climate change I
thank you for your commitment and your
desire to help support our communities
thank you for your advocacy thank you
for your commitment to making a better
world
yes indeed this is excellent work and I
am very inspired by everyone who helped
make this happen
but we here know that we cannot stop
calling for Action we know that we have
shown up time and time again and world
leaders are still not doing enough so
today we're gonna do a little chant and
we need them that we need them to hear
us loud and clear so I'm gonna ask what
do we need action action when do we need
it now what do we need action when do we
need it now what do we need action when
do we need it
thank you
my name is Louis Pugh I'm an endurance
swimmer I'm the UN patron of the oceans
and for over 30 years now I've been
swimming in the world's oceans and
rivers trying to shine a light on how
important it is for us to protect them
now behind me you'll see an incredibly
beautiful River this is the Hudson River
and it's one of the most incredible
rivers in the world I mean which river
starts high up in a Wilderness Area
where their turkey vultures beavers and
bears and ends in one of the greatest
cities on this Earth
and the reason why I swam 315 miles down
the Hudson was to highlight just how
important it is that we protect our
Rivers the health of the Hudson has
significantly improved in the last 50
years but we must remain vigilant
your voice matters
please welcome to the stage Global
citizen Ambassador science educator and
CEO of the planetary Society Bill Nye an
endurance swimmer and U.N patron of the
oceans Lewis Hugh
whoa I know it's wet Where You Are
I love that song check this out people
you may think you're wet but this man
just swam an average of five hours a day
for 30 days straight the length of the
entire Hudson River and an extraordinary
feat of endurance my friend that is
really something today
uh you've swapped your swimsuit but
given the weather I'm not sure you you
made the right choice maybe you should
have kept it on uh you're here with the
message of hope that we can protect the
world's Rivers precisely bill you know
50 years ago the Hudson was one of the
most polluted rivers in America
and a swim like this would have been
absolutely impossible
but in the 1970s New Yorkers said enough
is enough and they started cleaning it
up mile by mile town after town Factory
after Factory and they turned the fate
of it around
we must never become complacent when it
comes to protecting the environment and
we must always be vigilant
there is still a threat from sewage and
chemicals entering the river but I
believe the Hudson gives hope to people
all over the world that their Rivers can
also be saved
our Rivers sustain human livelihoods and
support countless
threatens their very assistance it
threatens all of ours too we can't have
a healthy Planet without healthy Rivers
they are the arteries of our world this
is why the rivers are life campaign
calls on world leaders to prioritize
clean rivers as part of their commitment
to protecting legally protecting at
least 30 percent of the planet by 2030.
[Applause]
[Music]
the bottom line is that all our Rivers
should be drinkable fishable and
swimmable
drinkable fishable swimmable let's go
please add your name to our open letter
on the global citizen app and urge world
leaders to protect our planet's rivers
and oceans so that we can secure a
peaceful and sustainable future for all
of us let's go
great to see you all great thanks for
coming in the rain you're used to it but
uh
I'm gonna head over here thanks you guys
[Applause]
right here right now we can eliminate
water stress
carbon traditionally dominates climate
crisis conversations and water is often
overlooked
worldwide technology is working towards
water neutrality while promoting healthy
sustainable and Equitable ecosystems and
by undertaking Lake and pond
Rejuvenation projects we're working
toward achieving our goals around the
globe
foreign
[Music]
famine this year will provide nearly 300
million euros to prevent hunger and
malnutrition globally
and will fulfill our pledge to provide
at least 225 million euros in
international climate Finance by 2025.
next year marks 50 years of Irish Aid
the Irish government's program for
International Development will continue
to work with global Citizen and our
International Partners to create a
better and fairer world
[Music]
rising sea levels intensifying
hurricanes wildfires floods and droughts
our lives and livelihoods and the Very
soul of our cultures are on the threats
this is why today
I'm honored to announce that Antiguan
Barbuda officially joins our Pacific
friends in calling for the negotiation
of a fossil fuel non-proliferation
treaty
this treaty will be more than words
it's a binding plan to end the fossil
fuel era
[Music]
foreign
700 million dollars in special drawing
rights which will help leverage an
estimated value of 1.3 billion dollars
to the international monetary funds
poverty reduction and growth trust this
is big this matters to me because it's a
promise to our shared Humanity when we
stand together we are unstoppable our
actions today shape a better tomorrow
for everyone
[Music]
flawed your efforts and I want
also doing its part that's why earlier
this week we announced the U.S
Department of State is committing 15
million dollars to launch epic the end
plastic pollution International
collaborative epic will challenge
organizations around the globe to
Champion innovative solutions to the
plastic pollution crisis
[Music]
let's keep taking action because when we
work together we can make real change
please welcome to the stage Conan Gray
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
like I never ending song
[Applause]
[Music]
the edges of your life
[Applause]
[Music]
can you make me stay forever
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
my name is Conan Gray
and welcome this is my very first time
here how y'all doing
I hope you guys are staying dry
so incredible to see so many people here
from so many different walks of life
taking action to end extreme poverty and
climate change
with so many of us here our voices can
be really heard we only have one planet
and if we come together like this we can
create a more sustainable future for us
and so many generations to come thank
you for being here
and let's continue to fight for positive
change
[Applause]
[Music]
but you haven't been back home for days
the pots and pans and roaches they're
glad I'm finally going cause even then
they shut her at your name
[Music]
you don't really wanna hear the truth to
you
it's always
[Music]
you let all you ever want is to be right
even if that means you got a lie to do
it
nothing you've proven
is that there's no one who ever has done
better and making me feel worse now you
really are the winner
yeah there's nothing that is
[Music]
now you really are
to say goodbye cause you're the winner
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
good
afternoon
[Music]
it's obvious to anyone who ever knew you
at all you ever wanted was to fight I
was only trying to survive the year
chaos
[Applause]
[Music]
now you
know
what you did now you really are the
winner
[Music]
like
we wish you the truth
to you
thank you
friends
[Music]
do you think I'm a joke
tell all of your friends
[Music]
told me tell me
[Applause]
[Music]
you just want far wrecked your car call
me crying in the dark
now you breaking my heart so I show up
at your place right away wipe its ears
off of your face
trash
[Music]
I'm crazy
[Applause]
[Music]
I love you baby
[Applause]
[Music]
one day
today
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you so much for having me
I love y'all so much thank you for being
here
[Applause]
[Music]
I still remember the third of December
me in your sweater is said it looked
better
[Music]
side what it is
like her better
[Applause]
watch as she stands with her holding her
hand put your arm around her shoulder
now I'm getting colder but how could I
hate her she's such an angel
but then again
[Applause]
[Music]
she's got you as my eyes
[Applause]
[Music]
pretty you gave her your sweater it's
just polyester but you like her better I
wish I were
thank you so much have a nice day thank
you
[Applause]
[Music]
the world is facing serious threats from
extreme poverty to criminal gangs to
climate change
only Progressive internationalist
politics can rise to these challenges
and deliver a secure future
to deliver climate security a future
labor government would grasp the
opportunities for jobs and our economy
of driving forward with action for clean
energy standing strong on the UK's
climate commitments and work with other
like-minded countries to create a global
clean power Alliance
what a performance by Conan gray
everyone Give It Up
[Applause]
I am a Stan I was excited to literally
down here just screaming with everybody
in the rain which by the way it is still
raining and we are all here together for
much more than just music all right I
have my friend here in Nisha and I want
to ask you what would you say to
somebody who hasn't yet joined the
global citizen movement yeah I would
tell them to download the global citizen
app and learn about issues like poverty
and also take actions that's incredible
and it's as easy as downloading an app
there's a community ready to get
involved
and we're ready to party with you all
right guys what did you think about that
fantastic every single person out here
in the in this rain today
in action to get here and you can do the
exact same thing like Anisha said just
download the app and we'll see you
it's a joint responsibility to provide
healthy lies for all our children for
that immunizations are crucial which is
why the global polio eradication
initiative and key Partners UNICEF and
Rotary International have supported
life-saving immunization programs for
decades
hello New York
at last year's Festival I had the
opportunity to announce 150 million
dollars on behalf of rotary and along
with our partners we've immunized more
than 3 billion children across the world
we still have a long way to go we need
to raise 1.5 billion dollars to get the
job done
UNICEF works with communities around the
world to help in coordinating the
procurement and delivery of vaccines in
2020 340
000 people died of cervical cancer 90 of
these deaths occurred in low and middle
income countries where access to the HPV
vaccine is really Limited in 2023 alone
UNICEF will supply one in four countries
worldwide with this life-saving vaccine
in 2013 we began our partnership with
the United Nations Foundation to launch
our get a shot give a shop program for
every immunization given at a Walgreens
store Walgreens donates the value of an
immunization to the UN foundation's shot
at Life program
through the program we have funded over
90 million doses of measles and polio
vaccines distributed to children around
the world
today the Helmsley charitable trust is
announcing a commitment of 3 million
dollars to support the global polio
education initiative
the case for adding polio is clear we
want to be part of this historic effort
Global Citizens take action for a polio
free world where all children have
access to life-saving vaccines
[Music]
please welcome director general of the
World Health Organization Dr Tedros
gabriaces polio Survivor and vaccines
Advocate Sophia Ibrahim and artist
producer and Ambassador for the recycle
to end polio project exile tetsuya
good evening New York
good evening
this week was a historic week for health
at the UN General Assembly
countries made major commitments to
develop a new Global agreement on
pandemics
to end tuberculosis and to make progress
toward this inverse and health coverage
but you don't need to wait for worldly
leaders to improve your own health
if you smoke you can decide to stop
you can decide to get vaccinated to
exercise more or to eat less sugar and
salt
this year is the well third organization
75th
birthday but instead of giving us a gift
I want you to give yourself a gift a
gift of better health because Hells for
all starts with hell for you who is
committed to health
the health of every person and that
includes finishing the job of
eradicating polio once and for all
[Music]
I am a Pollo Survivor I contracted it as
a baby in Somalia and became partially
paralyzed from the waist down I want to
make sure this doesn't happen to anyone
and using my voice as a global citizen I
call our world leaders to commit 1.5
billion in funding needed for the global
polio eradication initiative to end it
by 2026.
my name is excitedia good evening
yeah
I'm the Ambassador for the recycle to
end the polio project which donates
polio vaccine to children around the
world by collecting and recycling
plastic bottle caps from all over Japan
with love dream and happiness I hope to
see the United States and other nations
keep growing their strong support for
the fight to end polio
[Applause]
[Music]
pull your once and for all
thank you thank you thank you thank you
and enjoy the show thank you
non-profits are on the front lines of
the world's most pressing social needs
you donate to Great causes with the hope
that every dollar you give arrives at
its destination quickly and efficiently
what you don't know is that behind the
scenes many nonprofits are forced to use
Tech that charges ridiculous fees these
platforms can also be cumbersome and
hard to use causing non-profits to lose
valuable time that could be better spent
on their work non-profits are
responsible for some of the greatest
Innovation that's happening in the world
but their doors are closed to way too
many donors hundreds of millions of
people are using Technologies like
crypto or Apple pay and if Charities
aren't equipped to meet these donors
where they are then they risk being left
behind during the greatest wealth
transfer in human history by pairing
give Lively's powerful practical and
free fundraising technology with shift
4's industry-leading non-profit Payment
Processing we can accelerate social good
on a massive scale this is about
empowering non-profits and lowering
their fees to make sure more of what you
give will actually get into the hands of
the causes you care most about it's
about simplifying the lives of those who
dedicate themselves to non-profit work
allowing them to spend less time
navigating complexities and more time
making a difference
[Music]
Belgian Minister for
Federation I have the honor to announce
that in continuation with our previous
financing of unfpa supplies partnership
we renewed our commitment with a new
financing of 2 million euros for
2023-24 75 years ago the universal
Declaration of Human Rights made
Humanity a promise that equality freedom
and Justice would be the values that
drive a thriving society today and every
day we look to you no matter where you
are to use your voices and be agents of
change human rights should be everyone's
normal I am proud to confirm that we
will be providing financial support to a
global program working to address the
essential issues of children armed
conflict
for Malta protecting vulnerable people
like children has been and will always
be an overriding priority business is a
home away from home to thousands of
ukrainians forced out by Russia's brutal
War therefore for more than a decade we
contribute to the lifeline fund and we
will continue to do so we do this
because in Freedom We Trust
big Lithuanian Archer to Global citizen
Festival
kosova survived the last genocide of the
20th century in large part due to the
brave work of Human Rights Advocates we
are ready to give back by signing on to
Global Citizens package of commitments
for the protection of Human Rights
Defenders at risk today
the Republic of kosova is determined to
continue serving as refuge for those
everyday Heroes who put their own lives
in danger so the rest of us can be free
[Music]
the taking over action for Global
Citizens which is truly truly amazing
yes a reaction you take is supporting
someone around the world who needs help
the most you are so proud to have you as
a part of our community
[Applause]
[Music]
now we know that some members of stray
kids couldn't be with us today because
they are recovering from a minor car
accident and we're sending them all love
from afar but we are happy that three of
them are still able to be with all of
you today all right everyone give it up
for three ratchet
[Applause]
tonight
[Music]
[Applause]
seconds
[Music]
[Applause]
true
[Music]
[Applause]
true
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
yours anymore
loaded
numbers
[Music]
free Russia
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
wow
Global Citizens how y'all feeling
New York City makes a boy
[Applause]
all right a little introduction we uh
three Racha of striking
yeah
all right first of all we're so honest
to be invited at such a meaningful event
[Applause]
um there really aren't you know enough
words to express how grateful we are to
be able to join so many people here at
Central Park the symbol of The Gorgeous
New York City yeah
it's more than beautiful to be able to
spend this time together so what an
amazing afternoon yeah
yeah it's our first time performing for
the 2023 Global citizen Festival
since this is such a meaningful Festival
we just want to say thank you to
everyone who has joined us yeah
thank you guys
um you might have noticed that the only
you know the three of us on stage uh we
actually call it three rounds and we're
actually the ones who produced all the
Stray kids music you guys listen to
[Applause]
um well like other members unfortunately
weren't able to make it today uh we
promised that this is going to be as
explosive and energetic as having the
entire group here today
all right guys having fun
do you like it yeah
[Applause]
so we just performed three watch out
draws Upon Our younger days when we were
trainees and talks about how proud We
Are of how much we've grown as a group
like how this song Demonstrate each of
our unique skill sets we believe it's
important to express and access the way
what we want and do what we think is
right
that's right that's right um with this
in mind I think um everyone here today
is on the same page uh we are so happy
to be here with all of you who took
action with global citizen to earn your
tickets
thank you guys so much thank you so much
I mean you know uh there are a lot of
matters you know going on in the world
um climate crisis
Injustice poverty you know that you know
all these they need a warm helping hand
you know awesome love and support so we
hope you know to really act together by
raising our voices for world leaders to
here
yeah
the future is not far away it is the
president that will face us soon
so join us now for the future and while
we're here we must continue taking
action to make an impact
it is this small movements that once
joined will be able to change the world
on a bigger and broader scale that's
right yeah it's not that difficult let's
do what which can do in our own
positions
yep
um you know you know because there's a
saying you know one person can change
the world you know what I mean yeah but
to have you know all of you guys here
today that just means we have a really
big impact on the world yes
um you know the same goes for us you
know we really make music for the whole
world to hear and through our music we
want to give comfort and strength so um
that being said shall we move on to the
next song
[Applause]
all right next up is a song called
heyday
yeah
which is yeah a pretty powerful song
um that we made for a popular South
Korean television program called Street
man fighter so we hope you guys enjoy
are you guys ready yep I'm ready hey
guys ready
[Applause]
okay
[Music]
here we go
now
okay okay
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
five seconds
let's go
enjoy
[Applause]
[Music]
the Fidelity Mexico
look at your door
[Applause]
foreign
thank you
ready ready
[Applause]
[Music]
are you ready
[Applause]
all right
thank you New York City thank you guys
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
we live in a world that has the largest
population of young people in history
[Music]
young people are running some of the
most inspiring successful and effective
Grassroots campaigns worldwide but
they're not in public office and we need
to talk about why
[Music]
no better campaign is as important as
getting young people to believe in
themselves and their power to engage the
political process and change policy or
participate in politics
we want to encourage and Inspire more
young people to run for political office
in a world where young people are deeply
in search of Hope
this campaign provides that hope that
young people need
be seen be heard is so important because
the world is facing unprecedented
challenges actually we have got a group
of people who are passionate creative
and really want to drive change they're
young people
[Music]
please welcome New York Times
best-selling author actor and activist
Busy Phillips Reproductive Rights
Advocate BB Gates and United Nations
special rapporteur on the right to
health Dr Tia Lang mufu Kang
I'm busy hi I'm busy Phillips and I'm a
global citizen
so listen when I was 15 years old I had
an abortion and this isn't the first
time that I've talked about this
publicly it's not going to be the last
because as you all hear no women girls
people with uteruses are currently being
denied the right to make Health Care
decisions about their own bodies
and without bodily autonomy there will
never be true equality women and girls
everywhere share a common desire for
Freedom the freedom to protect our
health the freedom to plan our future
the freedom to make our own choices but
right now in this country the state you
live in determines if you have any
reproductive Freedom it determines if
you control your own body
more than
257 million women and girls worldwide do
not have access to any safe modern form
of contraceptions we have the power to
change this if we work together as
Global Citizens
we've already proved that we can create
change together and over the last two
decades maternal mortality rates have
dropped by a third but that progress has
stalled and in some areas it has even
reversed the denial of your sexual and
reproductive health is a violation of
your human rights it cannot be tolerated
we must demand stronger and better
resource Health Systems and we must
demand them now
unfpa the United Nations sexual and
reproductive health agency plays a vital
role in empowering women globally by
providing them with access to
contraception with enough funding
unfpa supplies could prevent 24 million
unplanned pregnancies more than 6
million unsafe abortions and over 500
000 maternal and child deaths in the
next three years
Global Citizens you have been taking
action with us to call on world leaders
and change makers to fill unfpa's
funding Gap you called for new
commitments from governments from the
private sector and philanthropists and
one leader has responded
High Global Citizens I don't often get
to share a stage with such amazing
performers but I'm very proud to do so
today and to talk about an issue that is
so important to me the global
contraceptive crisis
after all when we talk about birth
control we're talking about women's
power agency and self-respect right now
far too many women around the world want
access to birth control but they can't
get it
unfpa supplies is working hard to fix
that
with the necessary funding they could
get contraceptives to more than 30
million women and adolescent girls every
single year
that's 30 million women and girls who
could decide for themselves if and when
to have children
this week the Gates Foundation announced
we're committing 100 million dollars to
unfpa supplies over the next five years
and I'm glad to say that others are also
stepping up with commitments to narrow
the funding Gap so we can ensure women
and girls have control over their bodies
and over their futures
people are hearing your call Global
Citizens
we have the chance right now to help
millions of women build the future they
want for themselves and that gives me so
much hope
[Music]
let us make a promise today to protect
the world's most precious and yet most
endangered resource girls
[Music]
foreign
Carson
[Applause]
[Music]
how are we feeling Global citizen
in our eyes
[Music]
I don't know what's happening
I'm back home times
[Music]
future till I can't face them
down
[Music]
can you hear me
my fingers
[Music]
[Applause]
everybody
[Music]
back home
thank you
how are we feeling Global citizen
I want to hear that one more time I said
how we feeling
it's extraordinary
that all of you are here thank you
can we do something together on the
count of three
can you scream as loud as you possibly
can one two three
you sound so beautiful
it is an honor to be on the stage
it is an honor to share in this moment
with each and every single one of you
in this Endless Sea of Love
[Music]
today
we are united together
through the power of music
to change our world
what a beautiful thing
I stand here before you today not only
as a musician
but as an activist
a voice for every girl in every corner
of the world who is voiceless
so Global Citizens
right here right now let us be her voice
[Applause]
let us make a promise to her
to love her to see her to hear her
to protect her
I believe with my heart in my hand
that there is no greater force in the
world
than a girl with a dream and an
education
and today
it is our duty AS Global Citizens
to protect our world's most precious
most powerful
and yet most endangered resource
are girls
Global Citizens let's Close Our Eyes For
a Moment
and together imagine a world
where the dream of equality is a
beautiful reality
right here right now in the words of
John Lennon
let us imagine
[Applause]
[Music]
this
it's easy
[Music]
foreign
people
[Music]
peace
I'm not the only one
[Applause]
I hope sometimes
[Music]
with essential Park
[Applause]
[Music]
hunger
the only one
[Music]
I hope sometimes
foreign
[Applause]
thank you so much
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you
her death sparked a worldwide movement
women took to the streets removing
hijabs and cutting their hair in Acts of
defiance
[Music]
protesters from across the globe came
together to show their support
[Applause]
[Music]
one year later activists around the
world continue to show solidarity with
Martha amini and the women of Iran
[Music]
founder of the Iranian diaspora
Collective mulge modero an
iranian-american human rights Advocate
Sophia Kiani
[Music]
thank you
hey
[Music]
[Applause]
people in Iran have been protesting
every day in the name of Gina Massa
amini
[Music]
they're over the Islamic Republic's
oppressive regime
they are taking to social media asking
us for us for us to see them and support
them
the Islamic Republic has killed over 600
protesters 70 kids
they have disappeared and imprisoned
people unjustly
citizen journalism is the number one way
the world receives information about
what's really happening in Iran
but the Iranian government is shutting
down the internet
and banning social media
they are trying to stop this Freedom
Movement
woman life Freedom zanzendiki Azadi
[Applause]
gingian
[Music]
[Applause]
the government can try to silence voices
but never the collective spirit
my heart was forever shaped by my trips
to Iran by The Moments of graciousness
and love I experienced in a country
fractured by violence and political
turmoil
no regime can break the spirit of a
Nation
I hope to return to Iran one day to find
that the people are free
but until then I will stand with them
from afar
today I am joining the thousands of
women who have cut their hair as an
active protest
join me in standing in solidarity
thank you
[Applause]
right here
right now
[Music]
[Applause]
please welcome to the stage
award-winning actor playwright and
Global Citizen and un women Goodwill
Ambassador deny Guerrera and 2023 Global
citizen Prize winner in NASA umahoza
Grace
all these Global Citizens out here in
the rain because you care about sing
thank for being here
I've stood on global citizen stages in
Johannesburg in Accra
in Paris and I'm back here in my
hometown New York because we've still
got work to do to amplify the
underrepresented voices of the world
and right now countries battling poverty
are trapped in an unending cycle
directly caused by climate change
we cannot ignore the fact that these
vulnerable countries despite
contributing the least to climate change
are the ones impacted the most
ly country are the corporates and they
must pay for the losses and damage they
have caused this is why the climate
Advocates Believers action takers and
experts have launched the global youth
demand for cop 28. our demands are clear
we need a loss on damage fund to be put
into action immediately and this funding
has to be new transparent predictable
and Grant base we call for children
youth women a marginalized Community to
be active stakeholders in climate policy
and climate action
join ineza a brilliant Young
freaking woman
[Applause]
join her and her fellow Advocates to
demand climate Action Sign her open
letter on the global citizen app today
thank you Global Citizens we love you
right here right now we can connect the
continent
installing fiber optic cables in
underserved communities in South Africa
furthers equity and inclusion it Bridges
the technological and gender divides it
promotes education as well as job
creation and Harrod's investment in
African infrastructure through companies
like vumatal aim to empower the pillars
of society parents and their children so
that Generations have access to the
world and its information
foreign
[Music]
I don't know what to say really
we're in hell right now we can stay here
or we can fight our way back one inch at
a time
on this team we fight for that itch
with our fingernails for that inch
because we know when we add up all those
inches that's gonna make the difference
between winning and losing
[Applause]
and I know if I'm gonna have any life
anymore
because I'm still willing to fight and
die for that edge
because that's what living is
there's six inches in front of your face
now
what are you gonna do
[Applause]
foreign
Global Citizens please welcome Deputy
Secretary General of the United Nations
Amina Mohammed
[Applause]
[Music]
hello New York
you're really quiet today hello New York
[Applause]
come rain or shine
we are here because we're committed to
humanity we're committed to our planet
and what happens today is a reflection
of leaders meeting all week promises
made seven years ago and today we're
recommitting
we're recommitting to what the great Al
Pacino has said tell it like it is it's
half time we're down but we're not out
people are hurting people are hurting
mind and body and Wars are raging and
our planet has gone from warming to
Boiling
leaders are really struggling with the
use of their power to keep the promises
of the global goals
and they risk breaking that promise to
billions of people
the good news is we still got seven
years to go and every game is won or
lost in the second half
so what are we gonna do are you sitting
on the sidelines no
are you changing the world yes
I didn't hear you are we changing the
world
[Applause]
well at the United Nations we're joining
you we're mobilizing people around the
world we can't do this alone we need all
hands on deck and we need each and every
one of you we need leaders to urgently
tackle the climate crisis because we
can't win unless we stop our world from
heating up
we need leaders to bridge the digital
divide because we can't win if billions
of people especially girls are left
offline and left behind and we need
leaders to achieve gender equality
because we can't win when half the team
isn't even on the field
[Applause]
so New Yorkers it's crunch time but
crunch time is when Champions are made
Let's unite and fight together
inch by inch to keep the promise of
achieving the global goals by 2030. New
York are you with me
[Music]
New York are you with the world
thank you
I'm standing next to one of the greatest
Global Superstars
now you've been a great supporter for
Global citizen you were here with BTS in
2021 and you had a fantastic performance
and now you're back what makes you a
global citizen this is my second time
joining Clover season and I'm happy to
be part of it through music
amazing music that is now sixty thousand
people have taken action and they want
to end extreme poverty does that
encourage you first uh they're amazing
and Tech action is important and that is
exactly what they're doing
and as a global citizen myself I will
give my all on stage tonight yes
speaking of stage
what are you going to be performing
um maybe my latest single seven and
a few surprises okay first one here tell
the people let's have a great time
that's right
many of you were in Paris last June for
party specs for people and planets we do
believe that we have to find together
against poverty
climate change and for biology
this is why we want to take our path as
well and to follow up this efforts and
we decided to invest
150 million dollars
in the iPad the international phone for
agricultural development
France decided to host and organized
the 13th replenishment of iPad
and we launched now the auctions
by taking this commitment we will invest
this 150 million dollars in iPad for the
years to come in rural areas and the
poorest for hilarious this is
the biggest commitment ever for ifad I
count on you thank you so much
[Laughter]
[Applause]
please welcome 2022 Global citizen Prize
winner Barbie is kierdo and actor
Creator and activist Liza koshy
September is our action month it's also
Hispanic heritage mom shout out
[Music]
which means that people all over the
country are coming together and jumping
into action to raise support and
awareness and I'm here to do that too
there was a time in a life where I
struggled to put food on the table for
my family I was working and on public
assistance but it wasn't enough no
matter how hard I worked so I started
advocating it's not always easy for me
to share my story it started with me
fighting for my family but turned into
fighting for Global Solutions
today
that's right I am still advocating for
people with lived experience as a member
of President Biden's Council on Sports
Fitness and Nutrition
in my role at feeding America and
through all of my work tackling food
insecurity because no one in the world
deserves to go to bed hungry that's
right that's my Barbie and yet
735 million people are still affected by
global hunger and displaced women and
girls bear a disproportionate burden of
this crisis when food is scarce women
eat less and they eat last now we can't
let this continue to happen we have to
do something about it right
right now is the perfect time for us to
call on world leaders to address the
global food crisis we must urge them to
invest in agriculture and climate
adaptation which would help put an end
to hunger worldwide
so take out your phones right do what
she said take out your phones y'all get
out right now I see you it's not out yet
and join the face up to hunger petition
calling for a food system overhaul
that's right you take that selfie and
then scan that QR code on the screens
right now I want you to upload that
sweet little mug of yours to sign the
petition it is as simple as that now
this is going to send a message to world
leaders that they need to face up to
hunger I know how many selfies you took
tonight
if you're dripping makeup down your
faces take this one too okay the one
that creates the change you want to see
in this world so if you turn the camera
towards us come on turn the camera
towards us we'll get in your selfies too
it's gonna be an ussie all right look at
us making a difference let's go let's go
pose girl pose
girl pose girl post
[Music]
thanks y'all
[Applause]
foreign
working in Madagascar as general
coordinator since 2019.
we are living in the world of drought
anger and natural disasters that are
caused by the climate change
people in these regions lives their
lives depending on cultivation of food
and we had two years of drought where
there was no rain
we talk about something about Cyclone we
observed the ocean hour of houses
families stranded with children without
shelters Sandstorm or oceans always our
all the plantation and leave people in a
devastated ways of living where we see
severe malnourishment of children
globally does all over in the world we
need to have a drastic measurement to
save our planet
we are all in the boat and this boat is
sinking if we can't do anything now we
are nothing to give to our next
Generation what planet are we going to
give to them the planet full of
catastrophe so let's start now this is
the time to help and avoid the much
worse things that must come thank you
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
Global Citizens please welcome Jungkook
[Applause]
[Music]
reminiscent Edition
come inside
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
again
foreign
[Music]
thank you
wow
hi Clover Stephen
where are me
thank you for
attacking excellent to be here tonight
[Applause]
and let's
give
making an impact together too
sure make sure
everyone everywhere
has access to
their basic rights like code on
education
okay
[Applause]
here is my next song
stay with you
[Applause]
my first time
I
love you
[Music]
thank you for coming in the rain
I love you guys
[Music]
together
each other
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
sit down
again
[Music]
I am
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
we're rid of the world only
so much
[Music]
another time
my life
[Music]
another time
good morning
[Applause]
[Music]
every second
wow that was a nice surprise what
we were at the weather
thank you JK thank you shout out to the
Army
[Applause]
okay
I can't understand what
[Applause]
okay my last song
is a set of BTS Heats
permission to dance
Dynamite
and butter
thank you and enjoy the rest of the
night
see ya
let's go
[Applause]
[Music]
I
am
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
rock and roll
Keep Calm kick the drum running on Like
a Rolling Stone
when I'm walking home
[Music]
[Applause]
tonight
[Music]
[Applause]
please don't die so as we break down by
myself
[Music]
whoa
[Applause]
a smooth night better life
trouble breaking into your heart like
that
yeah
my mother
lucky I'm making you sweat like that
break down
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
precise
[Applause]
baby
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
yeah
[Music]
my name is Karine my name is Christina
I'm Anisha and I am a global citizen I'm
passionate about human rights and civil
rights I believe that everyone has the
power to make a difference and I want to
use my skills and talents to help create
a more just and Equitable world so I try
to tackle the issue of gender inequality
the issue that I'm passionate about is
girls education sending girls to school
means let's try and manage Financial
Freedom and ending poverty and the
actions I take includes providing
sanitary paths to school girls in Nepal
small actions especially Collective
action and contribute to larger positive
impacts over time and I believe that we
can make a difference and I'm committed
to doing my part
hi my name is Alexa and I'm a global
citizen I'm passionate about Taco in
issue of poverty the main way I like to
take action is by actually volunteering
this means Gathering supplies and
necessities and getting it to people
that need them everything I do I do with
the hope that I'm making a change
[Applause]
in October of 2017 our community
experienced the tubs fire
5000 homes were consumed by the fire and
22 lives were lost during that time
my dad's home was completely destroyed
by that fire industry all of the
surrounding neighbors that night was a
very traumatizing experience
this community that I grew up in and
knew so well to see it completely
flattened
it seemed like a bomb had gone off it
felt like we were in a war zone
one thing we're doing here at Pepperwood
is implementing prescribed fires
cultural burning and intentional fire
has been a part of California history
for thousands of years so fire on our
landscape is a good thing however these
impacts from climate change are making
these fires more and more extreme and I
encourage everybody to engage with their
local Community Reach Out volunteer
figure out what you can do and if we all
put our little pieces together to
minimize the impacts of climate change I
hope we can
succeed and continue to live happy and
healthy lives for both our wildlands and
our human communities thank you
[Applause]
please welcome CBS News National
correspondent and featured co-host of
CBS mornings Vladimir dutier 2023 Global
citizen Prize winner hashtana durani
Global citizen Ambassador Kamen and
human rights Defender Olivier nduleke
[Music]
foreign
good evening Global Citizens
let me hear you good evening Global
Citizens
it's great to see that the rain hasn't
stopped you all from coming out to help
end Global poverty
I've been a journalist for many years
and no matter the story I'm covering
whether it's about conflict natural
disasters or political unrest I always
meet Extraordinary People defending
their communities rights despite the
risk of persecution in many cases
worldwide countless Brave individuals
stand on the front lines of Injustice
even when they are forced to leave their
homes they continue their work from afar
these Global Citizens are fighting for
the world's most vulnerable people
many like me were forced to leave
Afghanistan two years ago we were
outspoken we were Brave and we stood for
what we believed in as human rights
Defenders we were committed to fighting
for education for girls and women in
Afghanistan and the Taliban did not like
that
some of us ended up in Exile like me
some of us are still in prison some of
us are still missing our lives were at
risk due to the work that we were doing
but we won't stop fighting for our
rights to education even if it means
working from across an ocean
[Music]
right on yes
Nelson Mandela spent 27 years in prison
for opposing South Africa's apartheid
system
Martin Luther King Jr went to jail 29
times
for standing up for civil rights in
America
Mahatma Gandhi
was arrested for protesting the colonial
government in India
we know these people in their stories
but we don't know the thousands of other
human rights Defenders
that have been detained harassed in
prison and killed for their part in
speaking out
we cannot take for granted the fact that
we can assemble in Central Park and make
our voices heard
so we got to take action till we see
change are y'all with that
yes
human rights Defender
from 26
from 26 country were killed in 2022
almost half of them were defending the
environment
a few weeks ago my friend Obed carafur
was one of them
he was killed while he was defending the
right of community and against illegal
resource extraction
in the last 10 years more than
200 park rangers in DRC in virunga
National Park they was killed because of
their work to protect our land currently
five human rights defender in the region
face Injustice
20 years centers we are asked for your
solidarity
[Music]
foreign
so I would like to end with keep the
spotlight on human rights Defenders it
shouldn't have taken a whole village for
me to stand here it shouldn't have me
being arrested for me to be worthy
enough to end up in the U.S so please
stand up with human right Defenders
please make sure that they end up in
countries where they can work for human
rights and work from across different
oceans thank you
[Applause]
Global Citizens please welcome 2022
Global citizen Prize winner Brianna
brewing and the president of timor-leste
Jose Ramos horta
[Music]
thank you Global Citizens
thank you so much for withstanding the
rain and being here with us tonight on
this important night
the climate crisis is a Humanity crisis
it's been packaged as this big
complicated thing that should be only a
concern of politicians and scientists
but at the heart of it it's as simple as
saving our homes
saving mine so we can save yours
I love New York
but it's not Samoa I will always want to
return to My Island and I have the right
to as do people in suvalu Pakistan Libya
and timor-leste
the fossil fuel industry and all
Industries whose systems were built to
put profit before people need to stop
this is why I'm a proud advocate for the
vital fossil fuel non-proliferation
treaty
Pacific Islanders are the canaries in
the coal mine warning the world of this
climate reality Global Citizens to save
the Pacific is to save the world
[Music]
stands in solidarity with Pacific
Nations and is formally joining the call
for a fossil fuel non-proliferation
treaty
its mission is simple to hold new fossil
fuel Ventures phase out the existing
ones and found a fair shift to clean
energy these treaty levels the playing
field with fell rules only this week I
announced a bold new initiative a
groundbreaking effort that emphasized
the need for just transitions in areas
rich in vital minerals which are often
fragile and prone to conflict
timor-leste is dedicated to preventing
chaos and turmoil in vulnerable Nations
affected by climate change and this is
pivotal moment in our Global mission
thank you and God bless you all
thank you
[Applause]
Global Citizens please welcome NBA
All-Star entrepreneur and philanthropist
Carmelo Anthony
[Applause]
it's 2023 and we're celebrating 50 years
of hip-hop
50 years of an art form that took the
truth and the break beat and turned into
a soundtrack of social change
through poet and lyrics that confront
racial inequality shed light on police
brutality and call out systemic
inequities hip-hop serves as a
compelling Testament to the profound
impact of music as a force for Change
and empowerment
be nice
a legend in his own right a true hip-hop
head and believer in all things that are
forming bodies has put together
something special for all of us Global
Citizens as a reminder that what we do
and say makes a difference
live on this New York City stage we're
going to celebrate where it all started
[Music]
[Applause]
yes yes one two one two what's up
everyone
New York you're still nice
we got a good Bob I want to bring some
friends out
ladies and gentlemen thank you to my
brother Carmelo thank you New York it's
good to see the whole city out here
standing together here in Central Park
are you having a good time making some
noise
when I was just 18 years old I produced
a song called self-destruction it was in
that moment that I realized that I could
use music
playing their role so shout out to all
of The Advocates out there all of the
activists and all of the artists who are
out here using their voices to make
change but somebody told me that today
is a celebration or we celebrate tonight
are y'all ready to party
I want to get this started I want to
bring out one of my friends let's get it
started with an artist out of Chicago yo
he took his music and made it his own
combining lyrical poetry with Chicago
swag and a dose of Consciousness ladies
and gentlemen my brother common
[Music]
when I see them struggling I come
touching on the people New York City
where you at
as we celebrate hip-hop
50 years be nice on the one and twos we
lift up our women we lift up our women
and celebrate
that you are the light
yeah
like this gotta be something for me to
write this queen I ain't seen you in a
minute wrote this letter and finally
decide the Senate signs still delivered
for us to grow together love has no
limit let's spin a slow forever your
heart is weathered by what studs did to
you I ain't gonna subtle I did it too
cause of your feelings I Handle With
Care Brothers recognize your life they
can handle the glare hey I ain't the
type to walk around with matching shirts
a relationship is effort I'm not your
work be the one to make you happy it's
hurt you the most the end is near come
close to the most high regardless of
what happened or him let's rely here we
go here we go
[Music]
celebrating Global citizen 50 years of
hip-hop baby yeah yeah let them know
about the lights
[Music]
be nice
right now I want to introduce to you one
of the greatest to ever join in hip-hop
from Brooklyn New York he goes by the
name of Big Daddy Kane the B.I.G double
DIY come on
let's go yeah yeah I'm ready look rapper
stepping chilling they want to get some
I'm the king so yo you know the outcome
another Victory they can't get with me
so pick a BC dick is your history I mean
you didn't poet to get lyrical for you
to beat me it's gonna take a miracle and
step it to me yo that's a horrible
competition I just devour like a pitbull
against such a Chihuahua but when it
comes to being dope damn I got it good
let me tell you who I am the
b-i-g-t-a-d-y-k-a-n-e dramatic H static
it's been like pretty I'm different so
don't compare me to another cause they
can't hang words to the mother and me
snap with the principle of this pedigree
so when I move on your rappers you
better be ready good job positions
[Music]
the name is Big Daddy yes big not little
something funny here's your walking
paper sign it take them all I need y'all
to say cause
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
one time
in the building tonight
let me hear you make some noise
[Music]
where's my change
hey
thank you
[Music]
make your noise with the incomparable
iconic one of the kings in this culture
Busta Rhymes
[Applause]
scared to death
[Music]
gotta listen to her videos
[Applause]
[Music]
put your hands with my eyes
[Applause]
let's go
say fired up
[Applause]
[Music]
turn it down
everybody in this Global citizen
celebration
I need you to do this with me turn that
music back up
everybody make something
ladies
[Music]
all right
Global Citizens
such an honor to be here tonight
[Applause]
I am tremendously grateful
to be on this stage
celebrating 50 years of hip-hop
and art form
a culture
that has Amplified so many causes and
Sparks so much change
Global citizen
be nice
Big Daddy Kane
[Applause]
Rhapsody
and All of You Beautiful People
representing our beautiful city
thank you all
for allowing us to be a part of this
moment of greatness in history
happy 50th to hip-hop
we love you
I go by the name of the nice and I'm so
glad that I could share this moment with
my family right here I'd like to thank
Carmelo Anthony my brother coming Big
Daddy Kane grab City split Busta Rhymes
for representing hip-hop culture with me
here at the Global Citizens Festival
Make some noise
and most of all I'd like to thank all of
you and the Global Citizens for all that
you do
keep speaking your truth and standing up
for what you believe and remember you
are all the difference the power to
change the world is in each and every
one of you thank you all thank you for
what you do thank you for hip-hop
culture and thank you for Global citizen
Festival Make some noise
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
is to power an inclusive future for all
and in that future Mother Nature has a
voice
[Music]
please welcome actor activists and
entrepreneur Sophia Bush and Cisco
Executive Vice President and chief
people policy and purpose officer Fran
katsudis
hello
[Music]
y'all by 2050 we could be unable to
produce enough food to feed the growing
population outdoor air pollution is
projected to become the top cause of
environmentally related deaths worldwide
and we could lose all of the world's
coral reefs
I don't need to tell you that our
planet's future can no longer be
guaranteed without action
which is why we're very excited that
this week the binded Administration
launched the American climate Corps to
help train young people like you to
tackle the climate crisis
[Applause]
this program could put 20 000 people to
work in its first year on projects like
restoring land improving communities
resilience to natural disasters and
deploying clean energy
this is a great step forward in tackling
the climate crisis but we also know we
need all sectors to be a part of this
movement
now is the time for the private sector
to set clear goals and help fund climate
projects that could quite literally Save
the Planet which is why I am so pleased
to be here with Fran katsudas Chief
people policy and purpose officer at
Cisco thank you Sophia
and you are so right the private sector
must play its part
at Cisco we've set a goal for net zero
emissions by 2040 and we're evolving to
a circular business model
and in 2021 The Cisco foundation made a
100 million dollar commitment to fund
climate Solutions over 10 years did you
hear that 100 million
give the climate all your money
we need to invest in Innovative early
stage programs around the world
an amazing example of a foundation
recipient is Cara solar which trains
indigenous community members as
technicians who own and operate solar
shuttle boats in rainforest communities
how amazing is that
[Applause]
[Music]
much like the American climate core this
initiative equips people with skills in
the clean energy economy while also
reducing pollution and deforestation
everyone this is just one example we
need to usher in a more inclusive a more
sustainable future for all
and all of that starts
with giving Mother Nature a voice thank
you
thank you
right here right now being stylish
doesn't have to cost us a planet
it's crazy and not intuitive but there
are more than 300 million trees that are
cut down every year to make textiles
that end up in the suit lining and the
t-shirts and the dresses that we all
wear canopy with the support of the
Cisco Foundation Works to transform
unsustainable Supply chains that are
currently driving deforestation and
Forest degradation because together we
can protect vital forest ecosystems
around the world
foreign
what an incredible performance oh my
goodness DJ D nice you kept us connected
through the pandemic and here you are
celebrating five Decades of hip-hop what
kind of impact have you seen music have
over the years and what impact does it
have right now I'll tell you this well
celebrating five years of hip-hop is
because I am a hip-hop artist first and
then DJ
um but the music the music listen we
needed music during a dark time to keep
us happy keep us Dancing Keep Us
celebrating and also as a reminder that
we are all a community so that's what
music did during the dark time it keeps
us solidified and together and of course
common you are no stranger to having
music have a social impact social
messaging and you are a global citizen
yourself what makes you believe in this
movement so much well I just believe in
the the fact that you have so many
people that come from around the world
from different cultures different
religious backgrounds
um and they really we really care about
actually seeing this world change for
the better when when your intention is
about love when your intention and your
focus is on love then you can be from
whatever different part of the world
different side politically but when you
come together for something to really
improve lives and you really care then
you're willing to sacrifice all your own
personal things and be here to in this
togetherness so when we say together we
mean it and I see people taking action
and um this Global citizen thing is I
mean I've been there in Paris I'm happy
to be here in New York
um celebrating it and I and I want to be
a part of the work you know
continue to stand in
vention to take action and Galvanize the
rest of the world to do the same Global
Citizens how are you feeling
[Music]
[Applause]
please welcome TV host author and undp
Goodwill Ambassador hudma Lakshmi
country director of The Hunger project
Mexico Montserrat Salazar Gamboa and the
VP of communications at concern
worldwide Candence Patel Taylor
hey everybody how you doing let me hear
some noise
[Applause]
in a world of Plenty like ours with so
many advancements I strongly believe
that no one should ever go hungry and
yet nearly a billion people experienced
hunger last year our Global Food system
is in crisis so it's more important than
ever to invest in sustainable locally
LED solutions to solve the complex
issues of hunger and poverty that's why
earlier this year City Foundation
launched its first ever Global
Innovation Challenge to find and fund
organizations developing innovative
solutions to food insecurity just like
these incredible people on stage with me
give them a hand give them a hand
[Music]
at the hunger project we strangle the
belief in the power of women and all
supporting and serving them benefits
society as a whole thanks to the funding
from City foundations will be able to
provide training and resources to
indigenous women in South Vero Mexico
and both them
left businesses this will help break the
cycle of extreme poverty and
malnutrition in their communities
gracias
[Music]
[Applause]
and I concern worldwide we are finding
Creative Solutions to malnutrition
maternal and child health care and
Disaster Recovery to help end extreme
poverty with the funding from the city
Foundation we will provide business
training nutrition education and urban
gardening support to small-scale food
vendors specifically women and young
people in Nairobi Kenya
thank you
all right you guys each organization
listed here is receiving a grant of half
a million dollars to Pilot or expand its
work improving food security and that is
a total commitment of 25 million dollars
to help increase food access
affordability and the Financial Health
of communities around the world so thank
you for being here
[Applause]
[Music]
right here right now we need to address
the global hunger crisis
nearly a billion people around the world
experienced hunger last year in response
the city Foundation launched its first
ever Global Innovation Challenge
providing 50 organizations funding to
catalyze solutions to increase food
access and affordability because
strengthening the physical and Financial
Health of communities is key to ending
hunger around the world
foreign
[Applause]
climate change has greatly impacted my
beautiful home my grandmother had a
thriving backyard gardens but due to sea
level rise which led to an increase in
Social salinity we're unable to Quant
and we have to depend on food cubes and
plant above throat and because of this
my people have to rely on imported foods
which leads to an increase in ncds such
as diabetes high blood pressure also due
to climate change there has been an
increase in temperature which has led to
frequent droughts what frustrates me the
most is that people are still talking
and they're not active they are not
effectively implementing and adhering to
the regulations to the policies all
climate change related
all that was set out in the Paris
agreement what happened to that
but I have hope I have a hope for my
kitchen that we can still save to life
and you know what it's because of the
youths the Next Generation the Future
Leaders and it is with this resilience
and the spirit and this passion then we
shall continue this fight
[Applause]
come on since
thank you
[Music]
standing alone
we're gonna dance
[Music]
the whole world
don't know
we're gonna dance some gasoline come on
everybody
[Music]
come on
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
sing with me
[Applause]
[Music]
I got everything I wanted
not what you think
I thought I could fly
so I stepped off the garden
and nobody cried
nobody even noticed
[Music]
I had a dream
I got everything I wanted
[Music]
as long as
don't wanna lie here
but you can learn to
if I could change
[Music]
I tried to scream
but my head was underwater
and they called me weak
like I'm not just Somebody's Daughter
could have been a nightmare
but it felt like they're right there
it was a year ago whoops but I don't
wanna let anybody know cause everybody
wants something from me now
[Music]
I had a dream
I got everything I want
what
and you say as long as I'm here no one
can hurt you
[Music]
but you can learn to
if I could change
[Music]
would I do it again
[Applause]
foreign
the co-host of CBS mornings and editor
at large of Oprah daily Gail King
I want us to realize a powerful moment
like the one we just saw Billy eilish we
are not here by chance every person
gathered here in Central Park right now
and it's at least 60 000 of us and the
million streaming from home are here
because they chose to actively
participate in the global citizen
movement that's what you did give
yourselves a round of applause
because you care rain can't stop us rain
cannot history is our greatest teacher
because it shows us a profound impact
that emerges when voices unite as one
from the Civil Rights Movement of the
1950s and 60s to the marriage equality
movement in the early 2000s these
moments proved that Unity is driving the
force behind the progress but it's also
very important to remember that not
everyone is able to gather in this way
to assemble freely we take that for
granted at such a large scale did you
hear at least 60 000 of us are here go
us exercising the right to freedom of
expression and Association so guys we
must we must keep speaking out and
taking actions Global Citizens because
together we can change the what
the world
[Music]
[Applause]
poverty isn't even something that should
exist in this world at this point
because we have wealth we have intellect
we have the ability to develop and
design and create whatever we want to
[Music]
some of you here right now were not even
born back in 1998 It Was a Very Good
Year why because the miseducation of
Lauren Hill
I loved it too
first came out but all of you can sing
her lyrics why because she transcends
time this woman is a true artist whose
music carries a message of Hope and
power that inspires all of us that's
Millions around the world I love this
record I love her I adore her please a
warm welcome for Miss Lauren Hill
[Applause]
please respond when I call your name
all right Kevin Charles Darius Boykin
Alicia Simon Phillip Valdez Gabrielle
Salon
Sutton and Corey Thomas
[Music]
Lauryn Hill
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
Hill this year
how you feeling
[Applause]
yeah
come on come on yeah New York City
I wrote these words
for everyone
[Music]
[Applause]
before we even start to play
[Music]
what is
he will be just everybody
[Music]
sometimes
tomorrow tomorrow
[Music]
[Applause]
Everything is Everything is
[Music]
you know the change
no matter what the crisis is Right Josh
we're gonna give God all the thanks and
praises
all
[Music]
Right tickets
come on let's go
Everything is Everything
is
[Music]
forever
come on over here
[Music]
everyday
[Applause]
[Music]
New York City Make some noise
hey
[Music]
I treat this like my thesis whether it's
happening broken down into pieces
introducing them produce words reviews
how I choose up this big like I'm choose
[Music]
I could pop it you can't stop it drop it
your whole Crews Michael Scott big like
particles
on the cover don't discuss the baby
mother this is something to start up you
can't tell me I witnessed first-handed
of candy can't stand and respect a man I
get thrown around the planet don't steal
people feel miss him from New York to
Israel and this is real that's what I
can make in the street pounds
[Music]
keep your eyes
out
[Music]
things will change
is
[Music]
there a song
so be in the church
the pillow with the
[Music]
weather for collecting residual support
144. they're here before this ain't a
battle this is
only active diplomatic immunity in every
New York City Community
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
my God
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
please
you don't want to hear my opinion
[Music]
again
don't you understand me
[Music]
some
songs
[Music]
really happy
oh
those words
[Music]
[Applause]
let's go
life and direct
full effect
[Applause]
[Music]
baby baby
no one loves
you're more than me
[Music]
silly game
hello
[Music]
hello come on
yes
hello
[Music]
oh it's crazy
I just can't be
done
[Music]
well don't make me
this is crazy
[Music]
for me cry for me cry for me you said
you died for me give to me give to me
why won't you live for me
why won't you live why won't you live
[Music]
this is crazy
where are you
[Music]
here
nope
[Music]
my world had moved so fast today
I pass that seems so far away and life
I can't breathe
[Music]
and every time I try to be
what someone else thought of me
so caught up
I wasn't able to achieve
and
Jesus deep in my heart
the answer
it was in me
and I made
my mind
if I
[Music]
am my own destiny
foreign
[Music]
to everything we used to be
I hear so many cry for help
searching outside of themselves
I know
that is strength is within me
and my heart
[Music]
what's up
my oh
[Music]
my destiny
[Applause]
well as you say New York City
[Music]
three weeks you've been looking for your
friends
easy you won't even
foreign
it's also Humanity
[Music]
some cars
[Applause]
[Music]
let's go
guys you know you better
girls some girls
[Music]
[Applause]
no
[Music]
let's go
so sometimes
[Music]
you know you better watch out some girls
some girls
[Music]
[Applause]
nothing nothing
[Music]
in the spirit
in the spirit of reunions
I brought a few special guests
[Applause]
okay okay okay
like I said
in the spirit of reunion
when you say New York City
turn off the mic bro yeah
turn up the mic turn up the mic how many
mics do we rip one attack should we send
many money
how many miles
they can try to do this for all the
wrong reasons seasons change my days in
the race but it all stays the same like
The Love Doctor Strange like it tame
like the rapper bring like a snapper
when they do that got
true that
it was you who wants irregular social
pressure
Runway system
you can't create you just wait to take
place
[Music]
your Anatomy
Minecraft
makes my constipated
[Music]
one day I have people live
in a million
now I got a record deal how does it feel
I'm never gonna survive unless I get
creepy
foreign
[Music]
prize will show up yes he did yeah yeah
yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
ice
exit the turnpike
[Music]
good morning
baby baby
in the morning how many times
[Music]
yeah yeah
Global Citizens what up
let me see you light up the place like a
Christmas tree right now it if you want
world hunger to be over like the place
if you want Africa to get their natural
resources
light yourself right now if you want
Haiti to control their own natural
resources lighten up right now light the
place of like the Christmas tree send a
signal around the world
Nigeria
friends
come on it's a Haiti in the Dominican
Republic
[Music]
and take it slowly ready
baby
[Music]
I'm ready
I play my enemies
[Music]
yes yes
put your hands
[Music]
baby
I'm ready
[Applause]
thank you
guys ready
[Laughter]
[Applause]
yeah yeah yeah yeah
New York City
[Music]
[Applause]
with his words come on come on
[Music]
me softly with his song Killing Me
Softly
with his song
telling my whole life
with his words
Killing Me Softly
with his song
come on
I heard he sang
[Music]
so I came to see him
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
oh
yeah yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
uh-huh
right about now
if you got love for the world let me see
your hands in the air right now
Global Citizens yo yo
I'ma say one more time Africa needs to
control their own natural resources
you know it bro you know it Haiti needs
a control they own natural resources
[Applause]
the world we need to stop family let me
see your hands in air right now
[Applause]
you know what this reminds me of
yeah
here we go
handsome hands up everybody we're going
in
yeah
turn it up everybody we go in there
[Music]
together
see if you want to see crack babies
[Music]
another before
I bless you guys thank you so much
Global citizen thank you
[Applause]
if you cheat toy let me see your hands
in the air right now
[Applause]
[Music]
Make some noise
[Applause]
all right
[Music]
Global Citizens please welcome president
of soccer in the world FIFA Gianni
Infantino and the motzepe foundation's
founder and chairman Dr Patrice motsepe
and co-founder and CEO Dr precious
Malloy motsepe
should we start
should we start should we start
Ed
okay hello New York
so every soccer fan will tell you that
the game doesn't stop when it rains and
today is no different I'm thrilled to be
here with you and proud to be standing
with two people who have made it their
mission to empower marginalized people
on the African continent and Beyond
Patrice hello New York hello
hi New York hello
we are from Africa the motsepe
foundation which is based in Africa is
partnering with thousands of poor rural
communities and the traditional leaders
in Africa to produce food and
agricultural products and to enable the
residents of these communities to become
self-supporting
precious improving education and
tackling climate change are important
focused areas for the mosite foundations
we are educating thousands of students
in universities in Africa and
internationally and preparing them for
new technologies and fourth Industrial
Revolution jobs
the planet now more than ever before
requires committed and effective Global
Partnerships and action to address
climate change
we have been participating with other
philanthropic organizations and partners
through breakthrough energy Ventures to
produce energy with zero emissions
global global citizens is about action
and more action to make the world a
better place humanity and all of us
together have the capacity to end
extreme poverty and hunger and to
provide quality education and good
health and to drastically reduce the
impact of climate change
okay so New York Global Citizens
together we can build a safer healthier
more sustainable and brighter future for
the Next Generation let's unite the
world let's unite the world let's unite
the world thank you let's unite the
world
thank you
Global Citizens
is
hey
y'all feeling yeah
I'm still bopping the Lord I Can't Stop
Moving Like This Global Citizens it is
an honor to Stand Here alongside these
remarkable Advocates can I hear it for
them please
that's right now we've seen how action
can create impact so if you haven't
already added your selfie to the face up
to hunger petition to end Hunger I'm
gonna do what Lauren Hill said I'm gonna
find you come on now
now is that was the time
hunger can no longer be the elephant in
the room we need to address this now
we've seen progress already with
commitments from France and Norway
making commitments to the international
agricultural development but we are
taking this rallying cry far beyond the
festival are we not that's right yes we
are
Behold our leaders accountable and
ensure that they deliver real
commitments by December that's right
when we all speak together they listen
so if you're ready to take action and I
know you are right go ahead
right
join us right now by scanning the QR
code and if you already did so well then
y'all better smile because y'all are
getting in mind come on come on
and do this let's do this everybody
smile behind me ready one two three
Global Citizens
y'all look good a little wet but good
thank you y'all have a good night
[Applause]
[Music]
please welcome Global citizen Ambassador
Bridget Moynihan
New York
[Applause]
we have heard incredible stories and
witnessed some big commitments on this
stage over the years and so much of that
is made possible thanks to our amazing
NGO Partners the support of these
Partners is so key to the success of not
just today's Festival but of the global
citizen movement overall it is this kind
of unwavering support and the solidarity
of like-minded organizations that
enables us to truly amplify our impact
and Achieve our common goals so we want
to say thank you to all of you for all
that you do so let's hear it everybody
let's say thank you
[Applause]
thank you
please welcome actress singer and
activist Sophia Carson and Global
citizen CEO and co-founder Hugh Evans
thank you
how we feeling
how we feeling Global citizen
[Applause]
[Music]
tonight you've heard the issues we're
all facing unfair barriers to equity the
global food crisis the urgent need to
address climate change and create jobs
but you've also seen the extraordinary
power of what happens when we unite when
we use our voices loudly world leaders
listen and they respond
we saw commitments from France and
Norway on food security from Belgium on
supporting maternal health and gender
equity and the state of para in Brazil
on protecting the Amazon these are
incredible but we need more world
leaders to heed your calls to action
where are the members of U.S Congress
willing to take bold action to protect
foreign aid where is the Australian
government when we ask them to support
smallholder farmers and where is the UK
in the fight against climate change we
have to keep taking action until our
world leaders deliver on their promises
luckily as we have all witnessed here
tonight Global Citizens are taking
action
[Applause]
but this cannot be where the action ends
at a time where some leaders are walking
back on their promises your actions
deliver impact so don't stop taking
action climate change can't hit pause
while world leaders get their act
together so don't stop girls cannot wait
30 years to go to school so don't stop
and the poorest people on Earth don't
have a decade to spare so don't stop we
have to take action now together
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
or without this moment
or this moment
children are doing this to
so what connects these moments these
movements these transformations
a thriving and open Civic space a place
to advocate for ideas and to hold
leaders institutions and companies
accountable we have to achieve equal
rights throughout history the only way
we have expanded rights is through
Collective action Through People Power
today movements around the world are
asking hard questions about
sustainability inequality and the
violence and oppression that still
exists
Ford Foundation as part of our long-term
commitment to protecting and expanding
Civic space and democracy we are
listening
[Music]
we all create Civic space together we
can keep it alive and vibrant and ensure
an equitable Democratic and prosperous
future for us all
[Music]
please welcome actress and Global
Citizen and undp Goodwill Ambassador
Connie Britton with environment and
Indigenous rights Advocates Nino and
Helena gwalinga
hi everybody
oh my God you look amazing
you're incredible for coming out here in
this rain yeah
[Applause]
oh it's so good to be here
so guys I want you to meet these
incredible women that I'm here with
they're from Ecuador yasuni yes
yasuni National Park in Ecuador is known
as the most biodiverse place on the
planet with more species of life than
any other place in the world
beneath it all is a massive reserve of
crude oil but now thanks to the
referendum that just passed that oil
will stay firmly in the ground
Nina tell them about it yes the victory
for yasuni was the result of Decades of
work led by the indigenous and
environmental movements in Ecuador
especially young people and women
[Applause]
yasuni's oil has been exploited for many
years but now thanks to the referendum
not only will the land be protected from
further harm but the oil companies will
be forced to leave
[Applause]
[Music]
world leaders have failed to keep their
promises to face out fossil fuels so we
the people of Ecuador have taken things
into our own hands the referendum was
the first of its kind but it will not be
the last right
[Applause]
young and Indigenous peoples know how to
take care of the planet we must respect
indigenous rights and protect those
defending the land
[Applause]
many powerful countries failed to show
up for the climate meetings here in New
York this week and others are still
allowing fossil fuel expansion in places
such as our home the Amazon
we need to hold these leaders
accountable if Ecuador can begin the
process of phasing out fossil fuels
others countries can and must do so too
so if we can take on big oil and win so
can you
so can you
thanks guys thank you
[Music]
Global Citizens please welcome see nice
come on
um
[Music]
tonight
have you ever
[Music]
miss it I need a prescription
I'm gonna ask you once again
are you having a good time Make some
noise
[Applause]
come on
[Music]
watch me
Dance the Night Away
[Music]
be nice baby nice baby
foreign
[Music]
if I'm dreaming
so let's just keep on dancing
[Music]
like the legend of the Phoenix here we
go come on
our ends with beginnings
what keeps the planet sinning
of the beginning
[Music]
to the Stars
be nice baby baby
[Music]
thank you
the present has no ribbon
your gift keeps on giving
what is this I'm feeling
if you wanna leave I'm with it
[Music]
we're up all night together
thanks again
[Music]
thank you
once again I go by the name of Dina's
thank you for having me here tonight
it's so beautiful with global citizen
keep doing your part thanks to each and
every one of you out there
enjoy the rest of your night tomorrow
[Music]
devil wishes
peace
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
Jordan pulling again
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
Global Citizens please welcome comedian
and actor Chris Rock
hey hey
are we set up
all right well thank you guys
for coming out
well thank you for all your service
and you guys got together and you did
what nobody thought you could do
you guys ended the writer's strike and I
thank you
I thank you all so now come to the stage
one of the greatest bands to ever live
you know the hits like breaking the girl
it's right it's right scar take out
other side ladies and gentlemen
competition stage the Red Hot Chili
bad boy
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
thank you
[Music]
what's up
Even the Rain cannot stop this group of
Global Citizens
greater shine baby we're here we make it
an impact as a matter of fact I got two
very good new friends that I just made
here Ethan and Marnie guys
to the people at home that are maybe
wondering like what can I do what can I
do right now to be a part of this
movement maybe to get there where
they're at next year what is it that I
could do right here right now to make a
difference when there's an issue that
you really care about go post about it
but don't just do that go beyond it put
the work in put the hours in and help
make the world a better place it takes
time but it's worth it yeah without
question with a question it's a matter
of like you know taking the bull by the
horns and really pressing into the thing
that you believe in but it's got to
start with your why right what would you
do morning you know no matter how old
you are who you are where you're from
you can be a citizen and you can really
start change and help everybody do that
yeah fantastic fantastic I mean as a new
father myself I look at my son and I go
man what can I do to equip him with what
he needs to make a difference and to
make an impact and that I mean just just
finding passion alone is obviously Prime
right that's key my my advice that I
give to absolutely everybody is what is
your why and today Roi is here using
music and art and love and people and
Community to unify and to make changes
drops man in the ocean am I right guys
who's ready for some Red Hot Chili
Peppers
I don't know I mean I I'm a 90s kid Ms
Lauren Hill
garage
the house down guys absolutely brought
the house Fuji
foreign listen you heard it here folks
it's time to take some action obviously
everybody's here is hungry for change
right change that we all need to see in
the world and what we need to do today
is figure out what our why is press into
it and make a difference guys give it up
for yourselves out here in the rain all
day
[Music]
we got Red Hot Chili Peppers coming to
you very very soon stay tuned
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
this is
the place
[Music]
go away
thank you
baby
[Music]
before
fulfill the nation
[Music]
feels
just like you
[Music]
how about you
somebody new
just like you oh
[Music]
but I don't care
[Applause]
[Music]
Can't Stop
music
[Music]
please
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
shame
[Music]
less
alone
with you
[Music]
dead
it is
[Music]
thank you
it's got to still wish you saw sarcastic
fluid
[Music]
s
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
mm-hmm
[Applause]
take it away
Chad defense
[Music]
again
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
and
[Music]
moves
in the state of Indiana
[Music]
simultaneous feelings
she
she preached it down your face
[Music]
she's a love of baby and fighter should
have seen it up when we got a little bit
technical
ities
[Music]
[Applause]
go
[Music]
to me
I never made it up to Minnesota not
before the man
[Music]
when I land
Ed
[Applause]
[Music]
found your screen peace
oh yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
all right
are you good
the one in front of you are you good
kind of a gray shirt you're good yeah
clear you well
outstanding how are you
[Music]
pretty good
drizzle
I like hydrating in the moment
I never met a girl named the moment
no
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
when I know that I really can't go to
the world once more time to do
[Music]
what is
inhale
[Music]
let's get one
day
[Music]
thank you
when to defend to women
[Music]
get up
this is
[Music]
insane
thank you
[Music]
to prepare
tonight
burning beautiful
[Music]
let me know
I love you
so much
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
got hammers in both my hands such a
delicate
[Music]
cause that made me tough
we don't remember me but what I did last
night
[Music]
we now remember me
it's only
1980. it's only 1983
spoken to be fun
feeling my own life
my brother's a keeper
I'm married to TV why
[Music]
why
did last night
[Music]
listen Lord I know
remember me
it's only 19 days
[Music]
the whiskey
trying to
trying
[Music]
down remember me
last night
[Music]
say hello
I'm talking baby
[Music]
remember me
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh Henry
thank you everybody for sticking around
to see us play in the cold climbs love
you so much
[Applause]
London
[Music]
songs
what's wrong
password
baby
[Music]
foreign
just honestly
[Music]
[Applause]
it's a real honor to share the stage
with Lauren Hill tonight very grateful
to play with her on the same bill
[Applause]
do you yeah you're into it
song from New York City
my friends told me that I'd be lucky to
have
a hacker
[Music]
all the friends I ever had that love was
never true
[Music]
never ever gonna let you
because I love
dream girl
[Music]
you make me
a dream come true
[Music]
don't neglect me
make me
feel every day
now
now A Dream dreams gone
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
if you want these kind of dreams
[Music]
by the location
occasion
[Music]
there when to break
moment
[Music]
vacation
thank you
[Music]
space
singing songs
[Music]
thank you
later
[Music]
never mind
not a little bit alone
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
performance
oh no I'm sure
[Applause]
Darius was fiddling with my beard
tonight
it was amazing he just looked at me with
those brow and he's just like
it was the highlight of my night
[Music]
check that out
yes
[Music]
heavy
waiting
yeah
up here
[Music]
we go
what's up
[Music]
hang on
ten minutes
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
let's say I'm here
[Applause]
[Music]
tonight
heavy flow
a bad way
[Music]
waiting
for you
like he said thanks for sticking around
thanks for your generosity we do
actually love you a lot
[Applause]
five five
one more time one more time
[Applause]
[Music]
let's do this New York City Style if you
had fun tonight I want to hear you say
yeah
now let's do that one more time I said
that's the sound of 60 000 people
Gathering right here on the Great Lawn
of Central Park to witness millions of
dollars raised to help end poverty and
to experience a full day of incredible
performances once again my name is Josh
Martinez of I heart radio and night
number two of our I Heart Radio Music
Festival is happening in Las Vegas so if
you're streaming right now on Hulu you
will watch it in moments one more time
if you had fun Make some noise
lemon I love you good night
[Applause]